5 WORDTAG O 83rd
6 WORDTAG O mind
1 WORDTAG O 429,449
3 WORDTAG I-ORG CBSA
1 WORDTAG I-PER Solano
2 WORDTAG I-ORG ASUU
2 WORDTAG O trouble-free
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hina
1 WORDTAG O 45.810
3 WORDTAG O agricultural
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Carnival
1 WORDTAG I-PER Papandoniou
2 WORDTAG I-PER Amy
1 WORDTAG O STRIKER
1 WORDTAG I-PER Duvillard
2 WORDTAG I-PER O.J.
95 WORDTAG O 3.
1 WORDTAG O 3.67
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chongqing
1 WORDTAG O one-third
1 WORDTAG O 50.51
1 WORDTAG O STEP
1 WORDTAG O 10,896
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stranksy
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Sumitomo
1 WORDTAG O 199.71
1 WORDTAG O .443
1 WORDTAG O continually
4 WORDTAG I-MISC County
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toomas
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Arsenal
48 WORDTAG I-MISC DIVISION
1 WORDTAG O bore
3 WORDTAG I-PER Herve
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Spal
1 WORDTAG O unknowingly
2 WORDTAG O STOCK
3 WORDTAG O infection
1 WORDTAG O extinguished
7 WORDTAG I-PER Teutenberg
1 WORDTAG O dilemma
2 WORDTAG O 6.96
6 WORDTAG O briefing
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
2 WORDTAG O .532
1 WORDTAG O 691p
1 WORDTAG O photographing
1 WORDTAG O fault
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Veliko
2 WORDTAG O spongiform
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dopita
1 WORDTAG O 9.85
10 WORDTAG O alliance
1 WORDTAG O helper
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wataru
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sultan
2 WORDTAG O cords
5 WORDTAG O establish
1 WORDTAG O porous
30 WORDTAG O estimated
1 WORDTAG O KICK
6 WORDTAG O protesters
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jemison
1 WORDTAG O PROGRAMME
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fournier
1 WORDTAG O ethical
1 WORDTAG O Sep.03
3 WORDTAG O ton
1 WORDTAG O description
6 WORDTAG O 70th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Talen
1 WORDTAG I-PER VOGTS
9 WORDTAG O aid
1 WORDTAG I-MISC for
1 WORDTAG O nominally
2 WORDTAG O 222
2 WORDTAG O younger
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Soybean
2 WORDTAG O contrary
4 WORDTAG O favorable
1 WORDTAG I-PER Meluawati
2 WORDTAG O 156
2 WORDTAG O rebound
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Indah
1 WORDTAG O Sixteen
23 WORDTAG O firm
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
55 WORDTAG O city
2 WORDTAG I-ORG CUBS
2 WORDTAG I-PER Domingo
4 WORDTAG O assemblies
1 WORDTAG I-PER Omloop
2 WORDTAG I-PER Watkinson
1 WORDTAG O STAYED
1 WORDTAG I-PER Alloush
1 WORDTAG O 345
1 WORDTAG O 12.225
1 WORDTAG O STG
1 WORDTAG O communicate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sali
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Videoton(*
1 WORDTAG O megawatts
1 WORDTAG O four-year-old
1 WORDTAG I-PER Glafcos
2 WORDTAG O BACK
1 WORDTAG O 21-11
1 WORDTAG I-ORG x-Club
1 WORDTAG I-PER Belinda
1 WORDTAG O blurted
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Steptoe
1 WORDTAG O captives
1 WORDTAG I-ORG HSBC
4 WORDTAG O married
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sound
1 WORDTAG O Packaging
4 WORDTAG O 140
1 WORDTAG O mutilating
1 WORDTAG O paramilitary
12 WORDTAG O cow
1 WORDTAG O crops
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
1 WORDTAG I-PER Akpoborie
1 WORDTAG I-MISC law
1 WORDTAG O STREAK
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siegfried
3 WORDTAG O 263-7
1 WORDTAG O 7.03
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Corporacion
2 WORDTAG I-PER Montolio
2 WORDTAG O shops
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Horizons
1 WORDTAG O symbols
1 WORDTAG O 111.2
1 WORDTAG I-LOC COLLECTIVE
1 WORDTAG O 138.0-149.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arrigo
1 WORDTAG I-PER West
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zalevskaya
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lecce
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AVIA
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dunedin
1 WORDTAG O +3,831
1 WORDTAG O 14-pct
1 WORDTAG I-PER Beser
1 WORDTAG I-ORG WEN
2 WORDTAG O steal
1 WORDTAG O 4:15.006
1 WORDTAG O ASKED
1 WORDTAG O curtain-raiser
1 WORDTAG O Nuclear
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Willem
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
131 WORDTAG O AT
2 WORDTAG I-ORG JORNAL
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Escort
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Indies
2 WORDTAG B-LOC OR
1 WORDTAG O encampment
2 WORDTAG O dyed
1 WORDTAG O 1300
1 WORDTAG O participant
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lanus
2 WORDTAG O spleens
1 WORDTAG O putdowns
1 WORDTAG O 125M
2 WORDTAG O withering
1 WORDTAG O 8,400
1 WORDTAG I-PER Levitt
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet-era
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Verona
1 WORDTAG I-PER Khalid
1 WORDTAG O three-engine
1 WORDTAG O 56,126
1 WORDTAG O definite
2 WORDTAG O see-saw
3 WORDTAG I-PER Smirnov
1 WORDTAG O 774
1 WORDTAG O hints
1 WORDTAG O blackmailed
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Taibe
1 WORDTAG O incomers
1 WORDTAG O warns
1 WORDTAG O Harvest
1 WORDTAG O economics
1 WORDTAG I-MISC All-Ordinaries
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ruhunu
2 WORDTAG I-PER Amrollah
2 WORDTAG O 2:28.98
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Kosovo
4 WORDTAG O unlikely
1 WORDTAG O 46.21
2 WORDTAG I-PER (
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thiry
2 WORDTAG I-LOC FORT
1 WORDTAG O integration
3 WORDTAG O Q1
1 WORDTAG O vow
8 WORDTAG O eating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Caesar
1 WORDTAG O 45.05
84 WORDTAG O half
10 WORDTAG O clocked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rusedski
1 WORDTAG O Analyst
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Madhumalla
36 WORDTAG O wickets
1 WORDTAG O 727
1 WORDTAG O surpasses
1 WORDTAG O 597
1 WORDTAG O 90-minute
1 WORDTAG O Pvt
1 WORDTAG O swore
1 WORDTAG O guess
20 WORDTAG O involved
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Mission
1 WORDTAG O 1,305
1 WORDTAG O photo-finish
1 WORDTAG O 521.15
3 WORDTAG I-PER Radulescu
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
1 WORDTAG O schemers
3 WORDTAG I-ORG VNU
1 WORDTAG O Jan-July
1 WORDTAG O Soldiers
8 WORDTAG O task
1 WORDTAG O sail
2 WORDTAG O saline
1 WORDTAG O complain
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Servicenter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wyludda
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marsh
1 WORDTAG O shameful
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Butch
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sells
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Dynasty
1 WORDTAG O Soon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Paulinho
1 WORDTAG O 2-136
1 WORDTAG O denouncing
1 WORDTAG O bicycle
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jaime
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Team
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Rep
1 WORDTAG O 20,530
1 WORDTAG O censors
1 WORDTAG I-PER Koprinovic
2 WORDTAG I-MISC North
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Division
1 WORDTAG O 27.25
1 WORDTAG I-PER Martinelli
1 WORDTAG O 20.21
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Diyarbakir
35 WORDTAG O started
1 WORDTAG O infant
3 WORDTAG O lone
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Gorgona
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Rouge
1 WORDTAG I-PER Orel
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Sofia
3 WORDTAG O cleric
1 WORDTAG O 7-283
1 WORDTAG I-PER Murphy
4 WORDTAG I-LOC SEA
5 WORDTAG O CONFIRMED
1 WORDTAG O admitting
8 WORDTAG O seedings
1 WORDTAG O 312-983-7347--
3 WORDTAG O arson
1 WORDTAG O 6.2
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mexican
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jiaxuan
22 WORDTAG O problems
49 WORDTAG O those
1 WORDTAG O Interviewed
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Tirol
4 WORDTAG O 14,775,000
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGELES
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Archives
1 WORDTAG O undone
1 WORDTAG I-PER Art
6 WORDTAG O SER
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Zealander
1 WORDTAG O cultivation
4 WORDTAG O warehouses
1 WORDTAG O 3/8
2 WORDTAG I-PER Coers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brunmayr
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Porsche
1 WORDTAG O acquitted
1 WORDTAG O formerly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Charmaine
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
84 WORDTAG O still
5 WORDTAG I-ORG NBH
1 WORDTAG O abdomen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Angelo
1 WORDTAG O 217
3 WORDTAG O debris
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BP
4 WORDTAG I-PER Franz
1 WORDTAG O AWAY
1 WORDTAG O 97.42
1 WORDTAG O 18.5
2 WORDTAG O 1-10-100
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wilkins
716 WORDTAG O by
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bavarian
17 WORDTAG O 1993
1 WORDTAG I-PER Grieg
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hinchcliffe
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
2 WORDTAG O 2130
2 WORDTAG O harassed
2 WORDTAG O round-trip
1 WORDTAG O relate
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mir
1 WORDTAG O tone
1 WORDTAG O Ranked
259 WORDTAG O 7
1 WORDTAG O 42.45
1 WORDTAG O 123,394
1 WORDTAG I-ORG PSE
1 WORDTAG O Gaseous
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kryvy
2 WORDTAG O patient
24 WORDTAG O 77
1 WORDTAG O 100M
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arlen
1 WORDTAG I-PER AKRAM
307 WORDTAG O I
1 WORDTAG O predicting
1 WORDTAG O off-side
1 WORDTAG O 32.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Giga
3 WORDTAG I-PER Alexei
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mujahideen
3 WORDTAG O full-year
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eddo
1 WORDTAG O Jobless
1 WORDTAG O quieter
3 WORDTAG I-PER CHRISTIE
2 WORDTAG I-ORG GAN
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hall
14 WORDTAG O large
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
1 WORDTAG O 5-6
3 WORDTAG I-PER Glenn
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Civil
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Crvena
1 WORDTAG O APPEAL
1 WORDTAG I-MISC MS-NBC
1 WORDTAG I-MISC du
3 WORDTAG O pre-season
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ohrel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AUXERRE
3 WORDTAG I-PER Weiss
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Watts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hameed
1 WORDTAG O revoke
1 WORDTAG O guides
1 WORDTAG O 61.00
1 WORDTAG O consideration
1 WORDTAG O 89.40
1 WORDTAG O 2-yr
4 WORDTAG O Series
1 WORDTAG O blockbusters
1 WORDTAG O insistent
2 WORDTAG O journalism
1 WORDTAG O beneficial
1 WORDTAG O raging
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
1 WORDTAG O vied
1 WORDTAG O divine
2 WORDTAG O 98.9
4 WORDTAG I-PER Kan
2 WORDTAG I-LOC HAARLEM
2 WORDTAG I-PER Frost
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hans-Otto
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Valuable
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Lahore
1 WORDTAG I-PER Griffiths
2 WORDTAG O decrees
10 WORDTAG O owns
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
3 WORDTAG O 18.0
1 WORDTAG O packet
2 WORDTAG O freight-tonne
2 WORDTAG O Majesty
1 WORDTAG O IF
4 WORDTAG O stick
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aryeh
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ro
1 WORDTAG O retook
1 WORDTAG I-LOC LEEDS
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhahran
24 WORDTAG O bond
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Criciuma
2 WORDTAG O replying
1 WORDTAG O highest-ranked
1 WORDTAG O Hopes
1 WORDTAG O coupons
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lausanne
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ISS
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bratislava
1 WORDTAG O 5-240
2 WORDTAG O unsettled
1 WORDTAG O directorate-grade
1 WORDTAG O 7:36.81
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greenville
2 WORDTAG O dependent
1 WORDTAG O pursued
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Planning
1 WORDTAG O liberated
4 WORDTAG O 33-26
2 WORDTAG I-PER Battersby
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Express
1 WORDTAG I-MISC BALANCE-Water
1 WORDTAG O recommend
1 WORDTAG I-PER Srutwa
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
1 WORDTAG O 105.07
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rickey
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Kigali
29 WORDTAG I-ORG SAN
1 WORDTAG O adulthood
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
1 WORDTAG O spun
2 WORDTAG O 50-75
1 WORDTAG O stupidity
1 WORDTAG O 32,000
1 WORDTAG I-PER Josef
2 WORDTAG O volunteers
2 WORDTAG O Bodies
1 WORDTAG O 837/763
1 WORDTAG O 14.828
1 WORDTAG O 85.26
1 WORDTAG O ponders
1 WORDTAG O Fear
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
35 WORDTAG O overs
16 WORDTAG O walked
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
1 WORDTAG O CLOSED
1 WORDTAG O headless
4 WORDTAG O crucial
1 WORDTAG O Monthly
1 WORDTAG O portrait
1 WORDTAG I-PER MEDVEDEV
3 WORDTAG O turns
1 WORDTAG O managerless
13 WORDTAG O ransom
3 WORDTAG O tbf
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
2 WORDTAG O rallying
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
3 WORDTAG O fixing
1 WORDTAG O reprisal
1 WORDTAG O enlistment
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
1 WORDTAG O 12.2
1 WORDTAG O 960,000
31 WORDTAG O death
1 WORDTAG O 1:52.318
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrika
2 WORDTAG O boycotting
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sokoto
2 WORDTAG O furnace
8 WORDTAG O tension
53 WORDTAG O near
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wath
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Riviera
1 WORDTAG O retaining
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
4 WORDTAG O hole
1 WORDTAG O mouse
3 WORDTAG I-PER Dahman
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hicham
4 WORDTAG O 16th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Foundation
1 WORDTAG O comprised
1 WORDTAG I-PER Malgorzata
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
1 WORDTAG O PRODUCER
53 WORDTAG O security
1 WORDTAG O inadequacy
2 WORDTAG O 487
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Former
5 WORDTAG O container
2 WORDTAG O ideal
1 WORDTAG O 12.70
1 WORDTAG I-PER Virna
1 WORDTAG O incorrectly
2 WORDTAG O vigilance
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Petah
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shay
2 WORDTAG O combatants
3 WORDTAG O rebellion
392 WORDTAG O 5
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Sidor
1 WORDTAG I-PER Margit
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pork
1 WORDTAG O wrecking
2 WORDTAG O 11.04
1 WORDTAG O south-west
1 WORDTAG O forfeiting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC President
1 WORDTAG O .589
1 WORDTAG O enemy
1 WORDTAG O beverage
2 WORDTAG O 30.AUG.96
1 WORDTAG O archive
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Prievidza
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Iscor
4 WORDTAG I-LOC NZ
1 WORDTAG O TRADE
1 WORDTAG O .565
1 WORDTAG O 1620
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG O 23.53
31 WORDTAG O coach
1 WORDTAG O nc=acomparison
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
1 WORDTAG O councils
1 WORDTAG O dodging
1 WORDTAG O eight-year
1 WORDTAG O cabaret
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chatichai
1 WORDTAG O 728-9559
2 WORDTAG O FRN
1 WORDTAG O 220,000
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Cometra
2 WORDTAG O stubborn
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northampton
3 WORDTAG O voiced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brumm
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
1 WORDTAG I-MISC FTSE-100
4 WORDTAG I-LOC ZEALAND
1 WORDTAG I-PER SORENSEN
1 WORDTAG O dislodge
2 WORDTAG O 147.159
1 WORDTAG O quartets
2 WORDTAG O shrub
2 WORDTAG O unbeatable
1 WORDTAG O distributes
4 WORDTAG O secrets
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
12 WORDTAG O history
1 WORDTAG I-ORG THINAKARAN
1 WORDTAG O soothed
1 WORDTAG O POINTS
1 WORDTAG O GOAL
2 WORDTAG O 281
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Parrots
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
1 WORDTAG O t-shirt
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
1 WORDTAG O 146.2
2 WORDTAG O boatman
2 WORDTAG O licensed
3 WORDTAG O releases
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Nebraska
1 WORDTAG O 20,605
1 WORDTAG O +7.3;-3.6
1 WORDTAG I-LOC RICHMOND
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nasr
2 WORDTAG O relive
2 WORDTAG O jammed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC program
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Shatoi
2 WORDTAG O designer
17 WORDTAG O thought
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ruud
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
1 WORDTAG O fulfilment
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Coal
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Whittier
5 WORDTAG O sending
1 WORDTAG I-LOC WEST
1 WORDTAG O corrections
1 WORDTAG I-PER P.V.
3 WORDTAG O lawsuits
1 WORDTAG O 8716
1 WORDTAG O firebreathing
1 WORDTAG O passers-by
3 WORDTAG O Delivery
1 WORDTAG O 385-1-4557075
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul-Salang
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bunol
2 WORDTAG O outscored
2 WORDTAG O 3,894.00
2 WORDTAG O Rapeseed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Moses
18 WORDTAG O rival
1 WORDTAG O rain-curtailed
3 WORDTAG O 5.60
1 WORDTAG O forecasters
1 WORDTAG O biologist
1 WORDTAG O handsome
1 WORDTAG O 14,153
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
14 WORDTAG O EPS
1 WORDTAG O misery
2 WORDTAG O 14,390.7
1 WORDTAG O 112.56
1 WORDTAG O oilfield
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Yorkers
3 WORDTAG O hardline
2 WORDTAG O 1844
2 WORDTAG O evasion
1 WORDTAG I-PER MCRAE
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shiohara
1 WORDTAG O 311.9
1 WORDTAG O decentralisation
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rupert
1 WORDTAG O opting
1 WORDTAG I-ORG SOKOLOVSKA
1 WORDTAG O Monsignor
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Glenview
1 WORDTAG I-PER REDGRAVE
5 WORDTAG O medicine
2 WORDTAG I-PER SCHUMACHER
1 WORDTAG O Surprise
1 WORDTAG O Looming
1 WORDTAG O 10-5
3 WORDTAG O umpires
1 WORDTAG O unjustified
2 WORDTAG O 12-1-41-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kurdistan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Naish
1 WORDTAG O 209
1 WORDTAG O undercut
1 WORDTAG O 3300
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
1 WORDTAG O daughters
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Channel
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ALLENTOWN
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hermawan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Moller
6 WORDTAG O scientists
1 WORDTAG O third-longest
1 WORDTAG O cart
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kilda
4 WORDTAG I-PER Yevgeny
2 WORDTAG I-MISC ARGENTINE
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
1 WORDTAG O 25.50
2 WORDTAG O bacillus
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Straits
2 WORDTAG O comprehensive
1 WORDTAG O differential
4 WORDTAG O feeling
4 WORDTAG O pool
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Lancer
1 WORDTAG I-PER Drechsler
1 WORDTAG O idiots
1 WORDTAG O 4950.000
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunfermline
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
1 WORDTAG O manipulation
1 WORDTAG O 3-0-17-0
1 WORDTAG O golds
2 WORDTAG I-PER Perelstein
2 WORDTAG O commissioner
1 WORDTAG I-LOC BISTRITA
1 WORDTAG O 1865
1 WORDTAG O scouts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wicky
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Charleroi
1 WORDTAG O 36.6
9 WORDTAG I-ORG MFS
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gale
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Reggiana
1 WORDTAG O A7E
2 WORDTAG O actively
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Block
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ibrahimi
1 WORDTAG O rents
5 WORDTAG O acts
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Twyford
3 WORDTAG I-MISC NT
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ruano-Pascual
57 WORDTAG O goals
2 WORDTAG O 884
1 WORDTAG O FREQ
1 WORDTAG O violently
5 WORDTAG O legs
2 WORDTAG O skills
1 WORDTAG O 1886
3 WORDTAG O clothes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Matusevitch
3 WORDTAG O existed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kamiel
2 WORDTAG O newsprint
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sociological
1 WORDTAG O Piano
1 WORDTAG O 13,102
2 WORDTAG O MEETING
1 WORDTAG I-PER Traore
1 WORDTAG O risked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kuhn
21 WORDTAG O food
2 WORDTAG O tamper
1 WORDTAG I-ORG RECORDER
35 WORDTAG O manager
4 WORDTAG O 5.50
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
1 WORDTAG I-MISC SBF-120
1 WORDTAG O savaged
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Code
1 WORDTAG O 28.0
2 WORDTAG O 35.0
1 WORDTAG O 13.37
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Banat
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ilke
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lisabeth
3 WORDTAG O 941-8100
3 WORDTAG I-PER Coughlan
1 WORDTAG O prey
46 WORDTAG O ahead
1 WORDTAG O downside
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Love
1 WORDTAG I-ORG HONG
1 WORDTAG O narrowed
1 WORDTAG O unflagging
2 WORDTAG O lineup
1 WORDTAG O 817.60
1 WORDTAG O heir-to-the-throne
1 WORDTAG O sticking
1 WORDTAG I-PER Enrico
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gray
1 WORDTAG I-ORG at
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lattakia
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Suedwest
1 WORDTAG O 182,887
1 WORDTAG O Offered
2 WORDTAG I-PER Flavin
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shehu
1 WORDTAG I-MISC BUNDESLIGA
2 WORDTAG O 3-1/2
1 WORDTAG O rubella
1 WORDTAG O ingrown
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Abbaye
2 WORDTAG O founder
1 WORDTAG O 1,750-hectare
33 WORDTAG O 54
1 WORDTAG O 19.92
1 WORDTAG O 27,535.5
26 WORDTAG O south
1 WORDTAG O unloaded
2 WORDTAG O 0400
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Scientist
1 WORDTAG O 3,250,000
1 WORDTAG I-PER Seedorf
1 WORDTAG O sentries
3 WORDTAG O karbovanets
1 WORDTAG O Adventurers
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hidemichi
1 WORDTAG O 12.83
1 WORDTAG O diplomacy
2 WORDTAG O disarmed
1 WORDTAG O colours
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dead
1 WORDTAG O mixers
4 WORDTAG I-PER Chiate
1 WORDTAG O 2,500-seat
1 WORDTAG O ground-floor
1 WORDTAG O IAE-3
1 WORDTAG O depot
1 WORDTAG O Collated
1 WORDTAG O www.internetstartup.com
1 WORDTAG O all-share
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hwa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dani
1 WORDTAG O includind
167 WORDTAG O 9
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ORVIETO
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Victoria
1 WORDTAG O 02/09
45 WORDTAG O hours
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lausgberg
3 WORDTAG I-PER Deby
2 WORDTAG O filming
1 WORDTAG O 2320.00
1 WORDTAG O mocked
1 WORDTAG O 22.94
1 WORDTAG O Referring
1 WORDTAG I-PER Henke
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Springfield
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Newark
1 WORDTAG O +3,428
1 WORDTAG O Playoff
5 WORDTAG O crowds
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gianfranco
1 WORDTAG I-PER Keter
1 WORDTAG O 1:55.371
1 WORDTAG O harrowing
1 WORDTAG O WEEKS
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Swiss
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wash
1 WORDTAG I-PER McKinney
1 WORDTAG I-PER Peeters
1 WORDTAG I-MISC INTERVIEW-T&N
1 WORDTAG O infamous
1 WORDTAG O 2,746
2 WORDTAG I-PER Klimis
3 WORDTAG I-PER Love
1 WORDTAG O PLANE
1 WORDTAG O immunizes
1 WORDTAG O dearly
40 WORDTAG O such
1 WORDTAG O HQ
2 WORDTAG O naked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Etienne
40 WORDTAG O past
1 WORDTAG O exercised
1 WORDTAG O 24-km
1 WORDTAG O pro-war
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wojtek
2 WORDTAG I-PER Markvart
1 WORDTAG O WORKS
1 WORDTAG O blockbuster
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BioVest
1 WORDTAG O 12.88
1 WORDTAG O 300th
1 WORDTAG O Statement
1 WORDTAG O 10.02
5 WORDTAG O fours
1 WORDTAG O NIS
3 WORDTAG O pension
3 WORDTAG O priority
4 WORDTAG I-ORG JOURNAL
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Mo
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Burundi-Central
1 WORDTAG O Hostilities
1 WORDTAG O reassure
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vitoux
1 WORDTAG O tirades
1 WORDTAG O 9.93
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maya
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mariusz
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Telfer
1 WORDTAG O horns
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Alexandroupolis
1 WORDTAG O .22
1 WORDTAG I-LOC HUNGARY
1 WORDTAG I-PER Olly
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahrain
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dacom
1 WORDTAG I-PER COCU
1 WORDTAG O uneasiness
1 WORDTAG O 44.92
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Avianca
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ploiesti
2 WORDTAG O 3.70
3 WORDTAG O pictures
27 WORDTAG O today
35 WORDTAG O period
1 WORDTAG O 02.777
2 WORDTAG O GAME
4 WORDTAG O killers
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Cup
1 WORDTAG O 349,000
1 WORDTAG O 23/96
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
1 WORDTAG O 20-6-70-2
1 WORDTAG O individually
2 WORDTAG I-PER Herman
1 WORDTAG O pipe
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gilardi
1 WORDTAG O 1,190
1 WORDTAG O 3:03
2 WORDTAG O DIES
1 WORDTAG I-PER Park
1 WORDTAG O .626
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jansher
1 WORDTAG O influenced
1 WORDTAG O similarly
51 WORDTAG O miles
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sacchi
1 WORDTAG O desert
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Montenegrin
2 WORDTAG O contingency
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kosice
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pakistan
3 WORDTAG O SIGN
2 WORDTAG O SHORT
1 WORDTAG O trademark
3 WORDTAG O blaze
9 WORDTAG O reasons
3 WORDTAG O 16,000
2 WORDTAG I-ORG IFK
4 WORDTAG O BALANCE
1 WORDTAG O implying
5 WORDTAG O soybeans
1 WORDTAG O 13.65
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pena
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tadeusz
1 WORDTAG O 10,119,000
1 WORDTAG O 1740
1 WORDTAG O regiment
1 WORDTAG O 8/30
1 WORDTAG O 8.26
1 WORDTAG I-LOC HEERENVEEN
1 WORDTAG O 422.1
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Neuchatel
3 WORDTAG O 7717
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ETA
2 WORDTAG I-PER Predrosa
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mariaan
1 WORDTAG O coordination
1 WORDTAG O intend
2 WORDTAG I-PER Berri
12 WORDTAG O cattle
1 WORDTAG O 242.94
2 WORDTAG O PAGE
3 WORDTAG O alight
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jonah
2 WORDTAG O immune
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Tadamun
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Gift
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Player
220 WORDTAG O when
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cofinec
1 WORDTAG O MIDDAY
1 WORDTAG O 38.1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Forth
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hart
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lareau
1 WORDTAG O confined
1 WORDTAG O 55,929.89
4 WORDTAG O formula
1 WORDTAG O 17th-ranked
3 WORDTAG O combines
5 WORDTAG O bureau
1 WORDTAG O 2,342.75
1 WORDTAG O 3,674
1 WORDTAG I-ORG SNCF
1 WORDTAG O outscoring
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Krakow
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
12 WORDTAG O recovery
2 WORDTAG O milk
2 WORDTAG O .539
85 WORDTAG O news
40 WORDTAG O signed
1 WORDTAG O Help-wanted
42 WORDTAG O head
3 WORDTAG O tasks
1 WORDTAG O SepOct
3 WORDTAG I-PER Robbie
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shriver
1 WORDTAG O 11,000
2 WORDTAG O PERIOD
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Province
4 WORDTAG I-ORG IRNA
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Phnom
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jodie
2 WORDTAG I-ORG TVX
6 WORDTAG I-ORG MSV
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hana
1 WORDTAG I-PER al-
1 WORDTAG O guitarist
1 WORDTAG I-PER Whittingham
35 WORDTAG O champions
2 WORDTAG I-PER Langer
10 WORDTAG O All
2 WORDTAG O ongoing
1 WORDTAG O internationally
2 WORDTAG O predecessor
2 WORDTAG O bang
2 WORDTAG O upward
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spence
1 WORDTAG O 568
1 WORDTAG O 4:21.715
5 WORDTAG I-ORG IMED
13 WORDTAG O unable
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Yates
1 WORDTAG O Reg
4 WORDTAG O singer
1 WORDTAG O 1:46.09
1 WORDTAG O advocate
1 WORDTAG O 33,000
9 WORDTAG O homered
1 WORDTAG O DECEMBER
1 WORDTAG O 25.75
2 WORDTAG O RE
2 WORDTAG O merchants
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Near
4 WORDTAG O barges
1 WORDTAG O 45.3
1 WORDTAG O One-month
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Minardi
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
1 WORDTAG O 2-mth
1 WORDTAG O Prosecutor-General
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
1 WORDTAG O 13-0
2 WORDTAG O 0.75
1 WORDTAG O 5500
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
4 WORDTAG O THU
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gradin
1 WORDTAG O --------------------------------
1 WORDTAG O Presidency
1 WORDTAG I-PER Teixeira
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leong
1 WORDTAG I-LOC IMOLA
2 WORDTAG O emphasis
67 WORDTAG O minute
35 WORDTAG O 29
2 WORDTAG O centrist
14 WORDTAG O enough
1 WORDTAG O 71.70
1 WORDTAG O vice-captain
1 WORDTAG I-PER Teravainen
4 WORDTAG I-ORG DE
105 WORDTAG O 70
4 WORDTAG O 2.20
25 WORDTAG O continue
5 WORDTAG O settlements
1 WORDTAG O one-kg
1 WORDTAG O cater
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fay
1 WORDTAG O Union
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Stock
2 WORDTAG I-PER Laca
1 WORDTAG I-LOC IL
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
24 WORDTAG O step
3 WORDTAG O benefits
1 WORDTAG I-ORG KONG
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Towers
1 WORDTAG O stationary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Griqualand
1 WORDTAG O ppm
3 WORDTAG O extortion
18 WORDTAG O sources
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
2 WORDTAG O 869.3
4 WORDTAG I-PER Knup
4 WORDTAG O implementation
1 WORDTAG O Diluted
48 WORDTAG O several
19 WORDTAG O issues
2 WORDTAG O circles
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam-Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG O lie
2 WORDTAG O 17.4
2 WORDTAG O 200-an-hour
2 WORDTAG O 1965
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nizhny
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bencevic
2 WORDTAG O b-1
3 WORDTAG O brain-wasting
1 WORDTAG O BULLION
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss-based
3 WORDTAG O 14,000
4 WORDTAG O 44th
6 WORDTAG O highway
1 WORDTAG I-MISC TriNations
1 WORDTAG O disillusioned
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vital
1 WORDTAG O 81-7
1 WORDTAG O defections
1 WORDTAG I-PER Milhaud
1 WORDTAG O passports
1 WORDTAG O 318
2 WORDTAG O ONE
1 WORDTAG I-MISC convention
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Lloyds
3 WORDTAG O announcing
1 WORDTAG O institute
2 WORDTAG O commentators
1 WORDTAG O 6,828,000
1 WORDTAG O mid-to-large
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pangalos
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Trax
1 WORDTAG O 0.35
3 WORDTAG I-PER Conroy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Birenda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jyrki
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Saskatchewan
3 WORDTAG O basement
1 WORDTAG I-LOC HELENS
1 WORDTAG O transfers
2 WORDTAG O three-year-old
1 WORDTAG O starker
3 WORDTAG O hair
1 WORDTAG O predicated
1 WORDTAG O saint
1 WORDTAG O editor-in-chief
4 WORDTAG O divorced
1 WORDTAG O fries
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisc
1 WORDTAG O Succeeding
1 WORDTAG O pastor
1 WORDTAG O nine-day
2 WORDTAG O Aa3
1 WORDTAG O high-performance
1 WORDTAG O 0.68
3 WORDTAG O dealt
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vince
1 WORDTAG O instability
5 WORDTAG O surrounded
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kaspars
1 WORDTAG O evident
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
2 WORDTAG O concessions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Serra-Zanetti
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lazarek
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Farewell
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wheaton
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
3 WORDTAG O approximately
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ignacio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wellman
1 WORDTAG O samples
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Homewood
4 WORDTAG I-PER Voinea
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arequipa
1 WORDTAG O confusion
1 WORDTAG O 9.0-12.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rupam
1 WORDTAG I-PER Udovenko
17 WORDTAG O form
2 WORDTAG I-PER Debbie
1 WORDTAG O Inaction
86 WORDTAG O June
1 WORDTAG O half-game
3 WORDTAG I-PER Indra
1 WORDTAG O hygiene
20 WORDTAG I-MISC CUP
1 WORDTAG O touching
2 WORDTAG O separation
1 WORDTAG O ailment
54 WORDTAG O report
9 WORDTAG O stable
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferro
1 WORDTAG O overbought
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lions
1 WORDTAG O 711
6 WORDTAG O pleased
1 WORDTAG O Thirty
1 WORDTAG O 0.8584
1 WORDTAG O thwarting
1 WORDTAG O revelled
37 WORDTAG O 9.
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Truth
1 WORDTAG O 25-6-95-4
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jerome
1 WORDTAG I-PER Glenallen
1 WORDTAG O Sister
2 WORDTAG I-ORG TBN
65 WORDTAG O league
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Balochistan
61 WORDTAG O run
2 WORDTAG O sadistic
2 WORDTAG O STRIKE
4 WORDTAG O 0.50
1 WORDTAG O two-headed
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Assn
1 WORDTAG O invade
1 WORDTAG I-ORG INDEPENDENT
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Western-organised
1 WORDTAG I-PER Seeliger
1 WORDTAG O Goals
1 WORDTAG O LUX
1 WORDTAG O 7-0-35-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Huddart
2 WORDTAG O 3548
4 WORDTAG O 41.0
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sciandri
1 WORDTAG I-PER Romero
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mines
14 WORDTAG O shortly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thul
2 WORDTAG O lasagna
62 WORDTAG O go
1 WORDTAG O publicized
1 WORDTAG O +
1 WORDTAG I-PER Webster
2 WORDTAG O fielding
1 WORDTAG O 1:56.830
1 WORDTAG O setback
4 WORDTAG O Goalkeepers
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bremen
1 WORDTAG O 965M
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nisbet
1 WORDTAG O sat
3 WORDTAG O farce
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Australia
1 WORDTAG O Fans
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperative
1 WORDTAG I-ORG VODNI
1 WORDTAG O lasted
1 WORDTAG O calmed
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mid-East
1 WORDTAG O Bright
5 WORDTAG O provided
3 WORDTAG O Members
2 WORDTAG O stealing
1 WORDTAG O 17-0-91-0
16 WORDTAG O measures
1 WORDTAG O detection
3 WORDTAG I-PER Roca
24 WORDTAG O director
2 WORDTAG I-PER Fabien
2 WORDTAG I-PER Maureen
1 WORDTAG O FIGURES
7 WORDTAG O selling
1 WORDTAG O 110.50
2 WORDTAG O oblige
2 WORDTAG O 13.18
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Olympiakos
5 WORDTAG O baby
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ileana
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Aussies
1 WORDTAG O pretended
1 WORDTAG O Preliminary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Eleusis
1 WORDTAG O sections
1 WORDTAG O vacant
36 WORDTAG O little
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Development
1 WORDTAG O 1980-88
6 WORDTAG I-PER McEwen
1 WORDTAG O charlatan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lazar
1 WORDTAG O unsatisfied
1 WORDTAG O bells
1 WORDTAG O albeit
1 WORDTAG O THREAT
1 WORDTAG O polishing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lviv
1 WORDTAG O scribble
1 WORDTAG O suspicious
1 WORDTAG O 1/9/95
18 WORDTAG O life
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
1 WORDTAG O 20,725
2 WORDTAG O 5.2
6 WORDTAG O education
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Imphold
1 WORDTAG O psychologist
1 WORDTAG O 95.7
2 WORDTAG I-PER Swardt
1 WORDTAG I-PER N.J.
5 WORDTAG O planes
1 WORDTAG O odds
84 WORDTAG O metres
1 WORDTAG O 10752.092
24 WORDTAG O penalty
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
11 WORDTAG O status
2 WORDTAG O denial
9 WORDTAG I-PER Smicer
4 WORDTAG O band
2 WORDTAG O 4-205
1 WORDTAG O demurred
2 WORDTAG O valley
1 WORDTAG O CHANGE
2 WORDTAG O contributions
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Vietnamese
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Rajavi
7 WORDTAG O amount
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aishwarya
4 WORDTAG O raids
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thily
2 WORDTAG I-PER Oremans
2 WORDTAG O deadlocked
1 WORDTAG O 0.73
75 WORDTAG O early
2 WORDTAG I-PER Owen-Jones
1 WORDTAG O +225
1 WORDTAG O shack
2 WORDTAG O viruses
1 WORDTAG O blanks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kapeta
4 WORDTAG O motorist
2 WORDTAG O favourites
16 WORDTAG O things
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mocude
3 WORDTAG O 409
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
2 WORDTAG O restitution
1 WORDTAG O considerably
4 WORDTAG O offenders
30 WORDTAG O train
1 WORDTAG O 2,558.84
1 WORDTAG O frees
1 WORDTAG O upright
4 WORDTAG I-PER Samper
1 WORDTAG O CART
1 WORDTAG O DISAPPOINTING
4 WORDTAG O coached
1 WORDTAG O gmt
1 WORDTAG O bedtime
3 WORDTAG O transmission
11 WORDTAG O means
1 WORDTAG O creative
1 WORDTAG O OctNov
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sask
1 WORDTAG O +41
1 WORDTAG O Bank
1 WORDTAG O indignant
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
3 WORDTAG O worsened
1 WORDTAG I-LOC OF
1 WORDTAG I-PER Carraz
1 WORDTAG O non-prescription
1 WORDTAG I-PER Corina
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Macedonian
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
1 WORDTAG O 8-284
2 WORDTAG O left-field
2 WORDTAG O 4-80
1 WORDTAG O Indeed
1 WORDTAG O 31.80
1 WORDTAG O cups
2 WORDTAG O youthful
1 WORDTAG O pumping
1 WORDTAG O immunity
4 WORDTAG O 382
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rabinovich
1 WORDTAG O 906
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bohinen
1 WORDTAG I-MISC RUSSIAN
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Loretto
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kwai
1 WORDTAG O Arguing
4 WORDTAG O access
1 WORDTAG O 83,008
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lori
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Gisenyi
3 WORDTAG O registry
3 WORDTAG O somewhere
1 WORDTAG O qrtly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Edhem
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reichel
1 WORDTAG O dignify
2 WORDTAG O 14-7
2 WORDTAG O DAYS
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Reina
1 WORDTAG O sadness
7 WORDTAG O hog
2 WORDTAG O Sheet
1 WORDTAG O 84.5
3390 WORDTAG O in
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bose
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BOLSWESSANEN
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Baker
1 WORDTAG O 1:56.417
1 WORDTAG O 151-to-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Medicine
2 WORDTAG O elaborating
1 WORDTAG O 42.
1 WORDTAG O 80.70
1 WORDTAG O surprises
1 WORDTAG O vetoing
1 WORDTAG O improperly
15 WORDTAG O State
1 WORDTAG O 1,074
1 WORDTAG I-PER NINE
1 WORDTAG O throughput
1 WORDTAG O EQUITY
1 WORDTAG I-PER Craybas
5 WORDTAG O larger
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kafawin
1 WORDTAG O tending
1 WORDTAG O implementing
1 WORDTAG I-PER HINCHCLIFFE
8 WORDTAG O skull
3 WORDTAG O bourses
1 WORDTAG I-PER Akira
1 WORDTAG O capita
2 WORDTAG O joy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Karl
6 WORDTAG B-ORG SPD
1 WORDTAG O 2:43.82
25 WORDTAG O wheat
1 WORDTAG O Draws
2 WORDTAG O perfected
1 WORDTAG O 1.4765
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Companion
1 WORDTAG O pioneers
1 WORDTAG O mandates
1 WORDTAG I-PER Citko
1 WORDTAG O disgust
3 WORDTAG I-PER Alomar
1 WORDTAG O CAMPAIGN
2 WORDTAG I-PER Grande
1 WORDTAG O racked
2 WORDTAG O Dollar
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Pierre
1 WORDTAG O enthusiastic
11 WORDTAG O improve
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gaidano
1 WORDTAG O 9-120
5 WORDTAG O warning
1 WORDTAG O filings
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lupu
2 WORDTAG O 41.5
1 WORDTAG O Outlook
2 WORDTAG O 3.7
2 WORDTAG O 4.38
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
1 WORDTAG O tea
1 WORDTAG O 39-32
3 WORDTAG O heavier
4 WORDTAG O lunches
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Broncos
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Constructorol
1 WORDTAG O burial
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Unit
1 WORDTAG O hickey-like
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Hitleresque
13 WORDTAG O religious
2 WORDTAG O villages
1 WORDTAG O 9554
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Studies
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Perm
3 WORDTAG O liabilities
1 WORDTAG O derision
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mieciel
3 WORDTAG I-PER McGriff
2 WORDTAG O .359
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hansen
2 WORDTAG O EXERCISE
4 WORDTAG O feared
60 WORDTAG O then
1 WORDTAG O 1.126
3 WORDTAG O defensive
1 WORDTAG O reinsure
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dubai
1 WORDTAG I-LOC GRIQUALAND
2 WORDTAG O felons
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pudong
1 WORDTAG O FULFILS
1 WORDTAG O unidentifed
1 WORDTAG O inflamation
1 WORDTAG O drains
81 WORDTAG O season
2 WORDTAG O drift
1 WORDTAG O Destinations
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Penrith
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jadida
1 WORDTAG I-PER Batigol
2 WORDTAG O ups
3 WORDTAG I-PER Benazir
1 WORDTAG O vigorously
1 WORDTAG O compulsory
1 WORDTAG O 804
1 WORDTAG O 23,500
1 WORDTAG O 5-7/8
1 WORDTAG O marine
1 WORDTAG I-MISC DAY
1 WORDTAG O square-jawed
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Essilor
4 WORDTAG I-LOC US
1 WORDTAG O problematic
4 WORDTAG O wilderness
1 WORDTAG I-ORG JOUR
1 WORDTAG O incitement
2 WORDTAG O launches
1 WORDTAG O WATCH
2 WORDTAG O SUPERBIKE
1 WORDTAG O thunderstorm
1 WORDTAG O cathedral
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
1 WORDTAG O 4.6200
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ulysses
3 WORDTAG O islands
2 WORDTAG O steep
2 WORDTAG O placing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Endrio
2 WORDTAG O 339-4
26 WORDTAG O keep
1 WORDTAG I-LOC &
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AGROTONZ
1 WORDTAG I-PER Younnes
1 WORDTAG O Exiled
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bongo
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
1 WORDTAG O rode
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fokker
1 WORDTAG O 128-1
1 WORDTAG O 0-50
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kareda
1 WORDTAG I-MISC IMKB-100
2 WORDTAG O attracts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Assad
1 WORDTAG O sound-track
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Mozambican
1 WORDTAG I-ORG ACES
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Aperto
7 WORDTAG O RECORD
1 WORDTAG I-PER Stubbs
1 WORDTAG O efficiency
2 WORDTAG O obsessed
2 WORDTAG O solidify
1 WORDTAG O sit
1 WORDTAG O commotion
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lausanne
1 WORDTAG O workplaces
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Libanais
23 WORDTAG O single
1 WORDTAG O core
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Azul
1 WORDTAG I-PER Egurugbe
1 WORDTAG I-ORG LIONS
1 WORDTAG I-PER GOOCH
1 WORDTAG O *INDICES
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nikki
1 WORDTAG O hardened
1 WORDTAG O pushes
1 WORDTAG O drive-through
1 WORDTAG O turnaround
1 WORDTAG O 61-year-old
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Petrobulk
1 WORDTAG I-PER Umberto
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanson
4 WORDTAG O patrols
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Climatological
31 WORDTAG O forced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siow
2 WORDTAG I-PER Quarracino
1 WORDTAG O 22.73
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Franklin
1 WORDTAG O dynamics
14 WORDTAG O veteran
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet-style
2 WORDTAG O downstairs
2 WORDTAG O labourers
1 WORDTAG O theoretical
2 WORDTAG O resumption
1 WORDTAG O TRIO
1 WORDTAG O 24.40
1 WORDTAG I-PER Peters
3 WORDTAG O year-end
5 WORDTAG O nominee
2 WORDTAG O 120.5
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
1 WORDTAG O SHARPSHOOTER
1 WORDTAG O glow
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ortelli
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Seaford
1 WORDTAG O under-fire
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pizzi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Venkatesh
1 WORDTAG O spurt
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Ansgar
3 WORDTAG I-PER Faber
1 WORDTAG O correspondents
5 WORDTAG O riders
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Athens
2 WORDTAG I-PER Voskamp
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Ill
1 WORDTAG I-ORG GENOA
1 WORDTAG O destroying
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leonid
23 WORDTAG O line
1 WORDTAG I-PER NEAGLE
1 WORDTAG O dossier
1 WORDTAG O 23.5
1 WORDTAG O islanders
1 WORDTAG I-PER CHANDA
1 WORDTAG I-PER Damion
42 WORDTAG O like
1 WORDTAG I-PER Moreira
17 WORDTAG O church
1 WORDTAG O cordoned-off
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Milan
1 WORDTAG O COMMUNITY
1 WORDTAG O briskly
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
1 WORDTAG I-PER Walsh
2 WORDTAG O thefts
1 WORDTAG O non-political
2 WORDTAG O pellets
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Constanza
3 WORDTAG O trln
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Wars
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ong
2994 WORDTAG O a
2 WORDTAG O captivity
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Cameroon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leslie
1 WORDTAG I-MISC LABOUR
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hammerson
2 WORDTAG I-LOC State
1 WORDTAG O 10.982
1 WORDTAG O 1986-87
6 WORDTAG O ferry
5 WORDTAG O sports
1 WORDTAG O half-yearly
1 WORDTAG O so-far
1 WORDTAG O symphonies
1 WORDTAG O new-found
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eldred
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sheriff
3 WORDTAG I-PER Esnaider
3 WORDTAG O origin
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hodges
37 WORDTAG O future
1 WORDTAG O 49.72
4 WORDTAG I-LOC MIAMI
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bosnian
1 WORDTAG O 1,236.5
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
1 WORDTAG O 16,300
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Macedonia
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stankov
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boonen
1 WORDTAG I-ORG TRINECKE
1 WORDTAG O TELEVISION
1 WORDTAG O favorite
1 WORDTAG I-PER Deere
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Karen
3 WORDTAG I-PER Klerk
8 WORDTAG O rare
1 WORDTAG O listless
1 WORDTAG O 49.48
1 WORDTAG O swollen
1 WORDTAG O ropes
4 WORDTAG O entry
4 WORDTAG O nationals
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sabourin
80 WORDTAG O during
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AND
2 WORDTAG O teenaged
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reynoso
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Procurement
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boudova
1 WORDTAG O Rev
1 WORDTAG O 1.56
3 WORDTAG O stunning
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
2 WORDTAG O SPREAD
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Velez
2 WORDTAG O 1994/95
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Ingaz
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Catalan
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shumer
1 WORDTAG O thorough
1 WORDTAG I-PER Guerrouj
1 WORDTAG O 8:12.04
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kukic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Savimbi
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AMR
2 WORDTAG O licences
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chenab
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Gateway
1 WORDTAG O knack
1 WORDTAG O .606
2 WORDTAG O prediction
1 WORDTAG O longer-dated
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rahul
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SOFIA
1 WORDTAG O networked
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Admira
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ingwe
3 WORDTAG O indifference
1 WORDTAG O rebuffed
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Reconciliation
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ceahlaul
2 WORDTAG I-PER Guivarch
1 WORDTAG O 962
4 WORDTAG I-ORG World
1 WORDTAG O overseers
1 WORDTAG O Depending
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SBC
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventude
2 WORDTAG I-PER Adel
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ove
3 WORDTAG O assessed
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carl-Uwe
1 WORDTAG O blazing
1 WORDTAG O oct
4 WORDTAG O Witnesses
102 WORDTAG O them
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Naberezhnye
1 WORDTAG O 267
2 WORDTAG O 101-member
1 WORDTAG O 4.40
24 WORDTAG I-ORG London
3 WORDTAG I-PER Neagle
1 WORDTAG O stirring
76 WORDTAG O took
1 WORDTAG O credits
1 WORDTAG O draconian
3 WORDTAG O claim
1 WORDTAG I-LOC UGANDA
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Impreza
3 WORDTAG I-ORG CBI
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
14 WORDTAG O activity
1 WORDTAG O hyper-inflationary
1 WORDTAG O 21-DAY
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Abidjan
1 WORDTAG O falsified
1 WORDTAG O chequered
2 WORDTAG I-PER F.W.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zejjari
1 WORDTAG I-PER Whiteman
3 WORDTAG O foil
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Banik
1 WORDTAG O penetrated
2 WORDTAG I-ORG BSM
4 WORDTAG I-LOC DETROIT
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marial
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Widad
1 WORDTAG O Anyone
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rydz
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Labour
1 WORDTAG O 2-19
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
1 WORDTAG O well-flighted
1 WORDTAG O 14-day
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunnes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vidigal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Guimaraes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rodimov
1 WORDTAG O 556.19
1 WORDTAG O rejects
1 WORDTAG O .592
1 WORDTAG I-PER Keane
2 WORDTAG I-ORG RMT
2 WORDTAG O 21.
2 WORDTAG O slept
3 WORDTAG O dry
1 WORDTAG O self-imposed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kundic
1 WORDTAG O ambassadors
1 WORDTAG O tides
1 WORDTAG I-ORG am
1 WORDTAG O .427
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nacar
1 WORDTAG O comi
1 WORDTAG I-PER MICKELSON
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
1 WORDTAG O solely
1 WORDTAG O phrase
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pendleton
2 WORDTAG I-PER Georges
30 WORDTAG O *
1 WORDTAG O five-metre
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Siam
5 WORDTAG O intends
1 WORDTAG O steers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Belcher
2 WORDTAG O insisting
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Advanced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aron
4 WORDTAG I-PER Gabriel
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Aarau
1 WORDTAG O much-postponed
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bestop
3 WORDTAG O cm
1 WORDTAG I-PER Auchard
17 WORDTAG I-LOC San
4 WORDTAG O justified
1 WORDTAG O nominate
4 WORDTAG I-PER Amr
4 WORDTAG I-PER Fulton
2 WORDTAG O 3.34
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ballace
2 WORDTAG O reformed
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hurte
1 WORDTAG I-ORG EXPRESS
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nocerina
2 WORDTAG I-ORG SRC
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
2 WORDTAG O searches
1 WORDTAG O seven-year-old
2 WORDTAG O lounge
2 WORDTAG O 3-116
1 WORDTAG O seven-inning
1 WORDTAG O rental
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Mahala
1 WORDTAG O hungry
2 WORDTAG O loser
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
1 WORDTAG O 8-
1 WORDTAG O 3:33.94
1 WORDTAG O 290.3
3 WORDTAG O recommendation
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Chornomorets
1 WORDTAG I-PER Facchinetti
1 WORDTAG O 21-day
85 WORDTAG O 71
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maru
1 WORDTAG O 4-200
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Sturm
1 WORDTAG O thrilled
1 WORDTAG O 0.03
1 WORDTAG O fifth-stage
1 WORDTAG O 1:58.579
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Trophy
4 WORDTAG B-LOC MT
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Country
3 WORDTAG I-PER Zicot
1 WORDTAG O pasta
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sebastien
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Dalian
51 WORDTAG O drawn
2 WORDTAG O 9-5
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mountain
2 WORDTAG O coaches
1 WORDTAG O honoured
1 WORDTAG O Repatriation
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Prairie
6 WORDTAG I-ORG CSU
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Slough
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Miguel
1 WORDTAG O 16.875
1 WORDTAG I-PER Neiland
1 WORDTAG O hindering
2 WORDTAG O Showers
1 WORDTAG O Secondhand
1 WORDTAG O cake
3 WORDTAG O rifle
1 WORDTAG O infiltrating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rostislav
1 WORDTAG O 5.35
2 WORDTAG O halls
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tanaki
2 WORDTAG I-MISC ROMANIAN
1 WORDTAG O samurai
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Hill
1 WORDTAG O megawatt
1 WORDTAG O 100=1992
1 WORDTAG O minors
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Canberra
1 WORDTAG I-ORG PA
27 WORDTAG O L
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gonzalez
1 WORDTAG O 22,666.80
3 WORDTAG I-PER Levenson
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Haiti
1 WORDTAG O possessors
20 WORDTAG O couple
27 WORDTAG O making
1 WORDTAG O 4.252
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
1 WORDTAG I-ORG EOE
1 WORDTAG O presents
5 WORDTAG O deny
1 WORDTAG O fanfare
1 WORDTAG O 28th-ranked
1 WORDTAG I-ORG KEKKILA
19 WORDTAG O remained
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
1 WORDTAG O nicely
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mandolina
1 WORDTAG O Bankruptcy
2 WORDTAG O s
6 WORDTAG O 1987
1 WORDTAG O galeforce
1 WORDTAG O 18:00
1 WORDTAG I-ORG ISLAND
2 WORDTAG O 6-1-17-0
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Justice
23 WORDTAG O armed
28 WORDTAG O rise
1 WORDTAG O Six-month
34 WORDTAG O order
1 WORDTAG O dishonourable
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
1 WORDTAG O 28:18.44
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nature
3 WORDTAG O proportion
1 WORDTAG O 732.50
20 WORDTAG O mission
3 WORDTAG O appoint
100 WORDTAG O 20
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Region
1 WORDTAG O swells
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barmasai
1 WORDTAG O 15-18
1 WORDTAG O Church
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
15 WORDTAG O fight
1 WORDTAG O FULL-YR
1 WORDTAG O untie
3 WORDTAG O shouted
1 WORDTAG O airbase
2 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGOLA
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rabat
3 WORDTAG O regulatory
1 WORDTAG O tax-exempt
1 WORDTAG O soliciting
1 WORDTAG O brigade
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Denis
1 WORDTAG O casting
1 WORDTAG O .426
5 WORDTAG O bottle
4 WORDTAG O +0.05
48 WORDTAG O IN
1 WORDTAG I-PER Artyom
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Gippsland
1 WORDTAG O 1,086
2 WORDTAG I-PER Tomasson
1 WORDTAG O Belgians
1 WORDTAG O 0:09
1 WORDTAG O one-run
2 WORDTAG O mills
2 WORDTAG I-PER Helder
1 WORDTAG O B-
2 WORDTAG O 38:32.719
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bunge
2 WORDTAG O skirmish
43 WORDTAG O agreement
1 WORDTAG O 2.79
2 WORDTAG I-PER Superman
1 WORDTAG O motorcade
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sheu
2 WORDTAG O telecoms
1 WORDTAG O rescue
1 WORDTAG O encamped
1 WORDTAG O teeth
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Stalinist
1 WORDTAG O weigh
3 WORDTAG O inspection
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kate
29 WORDTAG O An
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Beja
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
2 WORDTAG O reformer
1 WORDTAG O beats
1 WORDTAG O 109.36
1 WORDTAG O privatisatio
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Horst
1 WORDTAG O libero
1 WORDTAG O two-year-old
1 WORDTAG O appealing
1 WORDTAG O recreated
3 WORDTAG I-ORG UES
1 WORDTAG O Sixty
4 WORDTAG O 8.30
143 WORDTAG O could
4 WORDTAG O perpetrators
3 WORDTAG O demonstration
1 WORDTAG O cutback
1 WORDTAG O 41no
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Tacis
4 WORDTAG I-PER Talbott
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Togo
2 WORDTAG O cocked
1 WORDTAG O assaulting
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bombarda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eiden
98 WORDTAG O back
1 WORDTAG O 0.41
1 WORDTAG O 2.9
4 WORDTAG I-PER Pat
7 WORDTAG O equaliser
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Koeln
3 WORDTAG I-PER Malcolm
1 WORDTAG O SEPT
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sutton
2 WORDTAG O reviews
3 WORDTAG O cross-border
1 WORDTAG O radicals
2 WORDTAG O fearing
1 WORDTAG I-MISC DISTRICT
1 WORDTAG O Sergeant
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bhavan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kostantin
4 WORDTAG O respectively
4 WORDTAG O dystrophy
1 WORDTAG O 10.28
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stentex
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Col
7 WORDTAG O PM
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Piatra
3 WORDTAG O 582
37 WORDTAG O without
1 WORDTAG O ramshackle
42 WORDTAG O away
2 WORDTAG I-ORG ZTE
1 WORDTAG O Similar
1 WORDTAG O 981
1 WORDTAG O Unaudited
1 WORDTAG O rickety
1 WORDTAG I-PER McGrory
3 WORDTAG O SBPUs
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroecuador
1 WORDTAG I-PER Doohan
1 WORDTAG O redeemed
1 WORDTAG O bowlers
1 WORDTAG O latitude
1 WORDTAG O toast
2 WORDTAG I-PER della
1 WORDTAG O climate
3 WORDTAG O skin
1 WORDTAG O 5-67
1 WORDTAG O aspect
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Ekeren
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ackerman
2 WORDTAG O x
2 WORDTAG O contracted
1 WORDTAG O 115.259
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nixon
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Islamic
2 WORDTAG O GM
2 WORDTAG O Colonel
1 WORDTAG O SLIM
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
1 WORDTAG O 22.68
1 WORDTAG O Fiscal
1 WORDTAG O minus
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
1 WORDTAG O 9074.850
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Avalon
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
2 WORDTAG O 448
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dal
40 WORDTAG O army
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chalmers
2 WORDTAG O detailing
2 WORDTAG O calf
1 WORDTAG O provisionally
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pesalai
1 WORDTAG O mational
1 WORDTAG O 10.75
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BCH
1 WORDTAG O SAD
4 WORDTAG O 0-2
2 WORDTAG O payable
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
1 WORDTAG I-MISC ISRAELI
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NEUCHATEL
1 WORDTAG O Rev.
1 WORDTAG O analogue
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pelletreau
1 WORDTAG O 512
2 WORDTAG O overrun
1 WORDTAG O 172,580
1 WORDTAG O scans
2 WORDTAG O comparison
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chateaubriand
2 WORDTAG O avenged
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
1 WORDTAG O disqualified
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Southland
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pam
57 WORDTAG O 60
1 WORDTAG O BOSS
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bergen
2 WORDTAG O Imports
1 WORDTAG O unsympathetic
1 WORDTAG O BUT
1 WORDTAG O overhang
2 WORDTAG O 15.125
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Delmas
2 WORDTAG O gluten
1 WORDTAG O adrenalin
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wolk
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Independent
1 WORDTAG I-LOC SKOPJE
1 WORDTAG O 339.00
1 WORDTAG O apparatus
2178 WORDTAG O "
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Aleksandrovac
1 WORDTAG O 3,905.7
1 WORDTAG O convertible
1 WORDTAG O 4:19.762
2 WORDTAG O GETS
1 WORDTAG I-PER Carey
1 WORDTAG O walloped
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
2 WORDTAG O useful
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Machines
1 WORDTAG O slash
1 WORDTAG O shunt
1 WORDTAG O heifers
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamas
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Molde
2 WORDTAG O 1:04.541
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jockey
3 WORDTAG O Tomorrow
1 WORDTAG O 937.891
1 WORDTAG O 2:37
3 WORDTAG O faults
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican-controlled
1 WORDTAG O deaf
1 WORDTAG I-PER McGeechan
25 WORDTAG O problem
1 WORDTAG O best-selling
1 WORDTAG O offensive
1 WORDTAG O Reliever
1 WORDTAG O unpredictable
3 WORDTAG O 1.90
1 WORDTAG O dont
1 WORDTAG O 0172
7 WORDTAG O assessment
1 WORDTAG O Peacekeepers
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
1 WORDTAG O Tourists
8 WORDTAG O 280
2 WORDTAG O seller
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Wah
1 WORDTAG O THEIR
1 WORDTAG O 60.46
1 WORDTAG O *Note
1 WORDTAG O sportsman
1 WORDTAG O pantomime
1 WORDTAG O Inflows
1 WORDTAG O 3,060
1 WORDTAG O shuffled
2 WORDTAG O subpoenas
14 WORDTAG O V
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Pa
4 WORDTAG O approval
4 WORDTAG I-LOC ST
3 WORDTAG O incompetent
1 WORDTAG O 1:54.220
21 WORDTAG O cricket
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dole
1 WORDTAG O 598
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bundesbank
1 WORDTAG O TENDER
1 WORDTAG O Product
1 WORDTAG O .576
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Ffr
1 WORDTAG O endorsing
1 WORDTAG O franked
1 WORDTAG O upwards
1 WORDTAG O 2.24
1 WORDTAG O 1,185
1 WORDTAG O godfather
3 WORDTAG O hostility
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
1 WORDTAG O adoring
1 WORDTAG O Week
1 WORDTAG I-PER Marushko
2 WORDTAG O GEARING
1 WORDTAG I-PER Singh
1 WORDTAG O E-mail
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoists
1 WORDTAG O 222,457
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Five
1 WORDTAG O flare-up
1 WORDTAG O 1130
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nicholas
1 WORDTAG O 05:53
2 WORDTAG O 14.8
4 WORDTAG O manufacture
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Chong
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ginola
1 WORDTAG O state-controlled
3 WORDTAG O scam
1 WORDTAG O 95975
1 WORDTAG I-LOC PORTO
1 WORDTAG O all-party
1 WORDTAG O 10,725
1 WORDTAG O 340
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Times-Stock
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mustapha
1 WORDTAG O 2,355.93
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Metals
3 WORDTAG O emissions
3 WORDTAG O shotgun
9 WORDTAG O earned
1 WORDTAG O halfback
1 WORDTAG O constitutionally
3 WORDTAG O pornography
1 WORDTAG O 3-166
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Guineas
1 WORDTAG O batteries
2 WORDTAG O robbing
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ingrid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Miyaga
2 WORDTAG O convictions
1 WORDTAG O 2.58
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Coritiba
1 WORDTAG O educational
1 WORDTAG O potentates
6 WORDTAG I-MISC WORLD
1 WORDTAG O 15.75
3 WORDTAG O privately
2 WORDTAG O notified
1 WORDTAG I-PER Basie
1 WORDTAG O straits
1 WORDTAG O 15.72
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Werder
1 WORDTAG O cop
1 WORDTAG O designate
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Westminster
2 WORDTAG O Books
2 WORDTAG O 10.84
1 WORDTAG O 30,300-30,400
1 WORDTAG O 14-17
1 WORDTAG O adjustments
1 WORDTAG O blaming
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gordana
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lambruschini
1 WORDTAG O 10,925
2 WORDTAG O 17.8
2 WORDTAG I-LOC ALMERE
1 WORDTAG I-ORG democracy
3 WORDTAG I-PER Banda
1 WORDTAG O whipped
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ana
1 WORDTAG O punching
2 WORDTAG I-PER Redgrave
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cabinet
10 WORDTAG O billions
1 WORDTAG O 251/09
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
1 WORDTAG O seven-newspaper
1 WORDTAG O noteworthy
1 WORDTAG O lion
1 WORDTAG O merit
1 WORDTAG O prosperity
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
2 WORDTAG I-PER Cruise
1 WORDTAG O delivers
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Guinness
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Touchstone
1 WORDTAG O 33,230
39 WORDTAG O 40
1 WORDTAG O economically
1099 WORDTAG I-MISC _RARE_
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Internet
1 WORDTAG O slows
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
1 WORDTAG O skying
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
1 WORDTAG O 2/32
1 WORDTAG O 524.2
1 WORDTAG O UP-AND-COMERS
1 WORDTAG O jumping
306 WORDTAG O they
4 WORDTAG O complaints
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jalabert
109 WORDTAG O President
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Carril
2 WORDTAG O Word
1 WORDTAG I-LOC BERNE
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gebreselassie
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
1 WORDTAG O aloft
3 WORDTAG O luck
1 WORDTAG O 34-48
1 WORDTAG I-ORG KLADNO
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fac
1 WORDTAG O benched
2 WORDTAG O worker
1 WORDTAG O cash-related
2 WORDTAG O 107.55
1 WORDTAG O HEADBUTT
1 WORDTAG O pessimistic
2 WORDTAG I-LOC MUZAFFARABAD
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Saskatchewan
1 WORDTAG O unavailable
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunajska
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Alaska
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bernardo
1 WORDTAG O Fahrenheit
1 WORDTAG O Mrs
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Q4
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Free
1 WORDTAG O 1605
1 WORDTAG I-PER Adriana
1 WORDTAG I-LOC PHOENIX
1 WORDTAG O 3.85
1 WORDTAG I-PER Noon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pedersen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lamont
1 WORDTAG O 73.83
3 WORDTAG O Gross
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blank
1 WORDTAG I-PER Garrett
1 WORDTAG O disengagement
2 WORDTAG O tool
1 WORDTAG O 10,880,000
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fogarty
111 WORDTAG O him
2 WORDTAG O distributing
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Haladas
40 WORDTAG O c
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lago
1 WORDTAG O 7:47.78
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Galatasaray
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Croix
20 WORDTAG O products
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sawamatsu
37 WORDTAG O best
2 WORDTAG O Concern
1 WORDTAG O specifically
1 WORDTAG I-LOC NEUFCHATEAU
1 WORDTAG O FIGHTBACK
2 WORDTAG O hurts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kandir
1 WORDTAG O 4:16.141
1 WORDTAG O 50,000-seat
2 WORDTAG O thrusting
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stark
1 WORDTAG I-MISC MEES
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rutter
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Industry
1 WORDTAG I-LOC SRINAGAR
1 WORDTAG O dispatching
1 WORDTAG I-ORG EUROLIRA
1 WORDTAG O laughing
4 WORDTAG O NO
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Anhui
1 WORDTAG O 320
75 WORDTAG O number
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rysich
1 WORDTAG O Finally
2 WORDTAG O 1952
1 WORDTAG O QTR
1 WORDTAG O 5,350
4 WORDTAG I-PER Clarence
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Austria
1 WORDTAG O 571
25 WORDTAG O conditions
45 WORDTAG O work
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cecchini
1 WORDTAG O sucessful
1 WORDTAG O 9:30
3 WORDTAG I-ORG BARCELONA
2 WORDTAG O romp
3 WORDTAG O rewarded
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hansma
7 WORDTAG O copies
2 WORDTAG I-PER Henrietta
1 WORDTAG O 5-all
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hockey
1 WORDTAG I-PER Freeh
3 WORDTAG I-LOC OSLO
1 WORDTAG O optional-origin
1 WORDTAG O sanitary
1 WORDTAG O amputee
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rouser
1 WORDTAG O hand-written
4 WORDTAG O topsoil
1 WORDTAG O GOVT.BUDGET
1 WORDTAG O coverable
581 WORDTAG O 4
2 WORDTAG O 2.30
3 WORDTAG I-PER Susan
1 WORDTAG O oppositions
7 WORDTAG O asylum
1 WORDTAG O 816
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
7 WORDTAG O ensure
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
1 WORDTAG O headbutting
1 WORDTAG O nine-year-old
4 WORDTAG O scrap
5 WORDTAG I-ORG TV
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rudolf
1 WORDTAG O shaved
72 WORDTAG O foreign
1 WORDTAG O drained
1 WORDTAG I-PER Waterreus
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Cyprus-based
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
3 WORDTAG O FIXTURES
2 WORDTAG O Father
2 WORDTAG O pump
1 WORDTAG O 3:54.57
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fook
2 WORDTAG O spread
3 WORDTAG I-LOC LOUIS
1 WORDTAG I-LOC LAUDERDALE
1 WORDTAG O +0.9;+23.6
1 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Second
2 WORDTAG I-PER Eveningperformance
9 WORDTAG O knew
3 WORDTAG I-PER Springer
4 WORDTAG O agree
1 WORDTAG O April-July
2 WORDTAG O 219
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Matthews
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gerd
3 WORDTAG O updated
1 WORDTAG O daubed
1 WORDTAG O femmes
1 WORDTAG O ACCORD
1 WORDTAG O Scandal
1 WORDTAG O foods
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
2 WORDTAG O productivity
2 WORDTAG O sacked
1 WORDTAG O repurchase
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Loxley
2 WORDTAG I-PER Frazier
3 WORDTAG O 362
2 WORDTAG O warnings
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NEWCASTLE
1 WORDTAG O outdid
1 WORDTAG O Oldest
12 WORDTAG O 79
1 WORDTAG O Reigning
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kalashnikovs
1 WORDTAG I-PER Moira
1 WORDTAG O misleading
1 WORDTAG O Capacity
1 WORDTAG I-PER Burcin
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Tavria
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ganic
57 WORDTAG O make
1 WORDTAG O 33,149
1 WORDTAG O evaluated
3 WORDTAG O dogs
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Mentmore
1 WORDTAG O 5-3/4
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Lillestrom
1 WORDTAG O 35,563
1 WORDTAG O 15.5
2 WORDTAG I-PER Little
1 WORDTAG O Dozens
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
1 WORDTAG O amd
4 WORDTAG I-LOC STANSTED
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Victor
1 WORDTAG I-PER Griffey
1 WORDTAG O fortune
11 WORDTAG O determine
43 WORDTAG O plans
1 WORDTAG O 1,466.1
3 WORDTAG O 74th
15 WORDTAG O consumer
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Banking
1 WORDTAG O face-saving
1 WORDTAG O 170.4-175.0
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ikimi
1 WORDTAG O single-digits
2 WORDTAG O No.2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cloete
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
1 WORDTAG O 3.55
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Housecall
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MONTREAL
1 WORDTAG O rebels-Interfax
2 WORDTAG I-PER Torrens-Valero
1 WORDTAG O Nil
19 WORDTAG O sign
5 WORDTAG O .466
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Companies
1 WORDTAG O hurdler
1 WORDTAG O rentals
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Freeport
1 WORDTAG O lined
8 WORDTAG O extradition
2 WORDTAG I-PER Al
4 WORDTAG I-MISC et
1 WORDTAG O 1870
1 WORDTAG O tom
53 WORDTAG O agreed
10 WORDTAG O B
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Malbak
1 WORDTAG O tankage
1 WORDTAG O 14.18
1 WORDTAG O nerves
1 WORDTAG O Govt.Fcast
1 WORDTAG O FORECAST-
4 WORDTAG O slowly
1 WORDTAG O journeyed
3 WORDTAG O eighth-seeded
356 WORDTAG O --
1 WORDTAG O meanwhile
2 WORDTAG O Gasoline
4 WORDTAG O 1947
2 WORDTAG O upgraded
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boeta
1 WORDTAG O tranfers
2 WORDTAG O six-year
1 WORDTAG O 8863
1 WORDTAG O 13,091,000
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AGF-IART
1 WORDTAG O 27,600
1 WORDTAG O vice-chairmen
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
3 WORDTAG O 462
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pattaya
2 WORDTAG I-MISC BRAZILIAN
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Torshina
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rainier
1 WORDTAG O 113.02
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Purdue
4 WORDTAG O undertaking
3 WORDTAG O funded
4 WORDTAG O landless
2 WORDTAG I-ORG MTK
1 WORDTAG I-PER Victor
2 WORDTAG O 98
1 WORDTAG O 8.50
1 WORDTAG I-ORG FERENCVAROS
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sameh
2 WORDTAG O yields
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mandsaur
1 WORDTAG O 1200
4 WORDTAG I-PER Museeuw
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mae
2 WORDTAG O 7,149
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maslowe
1 WORDTAG O expert
1 WORDTAG I-ORG ERP
1 WORDTAG O independence-joke
2 WORDTAG I-PER Prinosil
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vierklau
1 WORDTAG O ubiquitious
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Leonean
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Brotherhood
1 WORDTAG O steady-higher
86 WORDTAG O They
1 WORDTAG O tenor
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gcaleka
1 WORDTAG O Lumber
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fatos
2 WORDTAG O three-party
1 WORDTAG O 574
2 WORDTAG O addressing
1 WORDTAG O exist
1 WORDTAG O straight-run
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mendy
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kris
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
21 WORDTAG O stocks
2 WORDTAG O 9-15
1 WORDTAG O suggests
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
1 WORDTAG O 4:19.808
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shinichi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aznar
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
1 WORDTAG O booking
12 WORDTAG O income
2 WORDTAG O chip
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
1 WORDTAG O ski
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Altamira
71 WORDTAG O international
1 WORDTAG O ex-dividend
1 WORDTAG O stemming
1 WORDTAG O kids
1 WORDTAG I-PER Burks
12 WORDTAG O resume
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Apparel
1 WORDTAG I-PER Danielyan
1 WORDTAG O Saboteurs
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toubon
1 WORDTAG O 125.3
1 WORDTAG O 4,153,800
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Taiwanese
1 WORDTAG O Mother
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nissan
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Itami
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sadiki
3 WORDTAG I-MISC 310
1 WORDTAG I-ORG is
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rinaldi
1 WORDTAG O preside
1 WORDTAG O elephants
1 WORDTAG O 12,300
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royal
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Moslem-Croat
1 WORDTAG O 83,801
2 WORDTAG O bridge
1 WORDTAG O 4-4
2 WORDTAG O Production
1 WORDTAG O 1-129
1 WORDTAG O 9,306,000
9 WORDTAG O lose
2 WORDTAG O operators
1 WORDTAG O twenty-second
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rosemary
1 WORDTAG O 31,412
1 WORDTAG O 1:02.795
5 WORDTAG O owners
1 WORDTAG O value-added
1 WORDTAG I-PER OLAZABAL
1 WORDTAG O 8.10
1 WORDTAG O hindered
1 WORDTAG O profession
1 WORDTAG O sacks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agnes
13 WORDTAG I-MISC FRENCH
1 WORDTAG O veiled
2 WORDTAG O stationery
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Zimbabwean
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
1 WORDTAG O 5.67
1 WORDTAG O Free
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Alkmaar
1 WORDTAG O 236-4
2 WORDTAG O stationed
3 WORDTAG O predicted
37 WORDTAG O club
2 WORDTAG O swimmer
1 WORDTAG O wheels
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hatoyama
2 WORDTAG O placards
1 WORDTAG O 27.5
1 WORDTAG O overmatched
1 WORDTAG O marketings
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lyngby
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
1 WORDTAG O ravine
1 WORDTAG O bench
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Muzaffarabad
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Aviation
8 WORDTAG O handling
3 WORDTAG I-LOC JANEIRO
1 WORDTAG O mid-sea
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
1 WORDTAG O 5-18
1 WORDTAG O W125
1 WORDTAG O FORCED
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Buzuku
1 WORDTAG O casinos
1 WORDTAG O MS
2 WORDTAG O 2,017.99
3 WORDTAG I-PER Steven
1 WORDTAG O domiciled
4 WORDTAG O School
1 WORDTAG O 44.3
2 WORDTAG O keenness
1 WORDTAG O 55.99
1 WORDTAG O infections
1 WORDTAG O +168,130
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Stuttgart
3 WORDTAG O restore
1 WORDTAG O wit
3 WORDTAG O BORROWER
1 WORDTAG O shrugged-off
122 WORDTAG O there
1 WORDTAG O wagons
1 WORDTAG O pre-election
1 WORDTAG O Opinion
1 WORDTAG O beta-1b
1 WORDTAG O rock-bottom
1 WORDTAG O 1633
3 WORDTAG O dying
2 WORDTAG O cleaning
3 WORDTAG O facility
71 WORDTAG O 100
11 WORDTAG O spent
37 WORDTAG O available
2 WORDTAG O 6,500
1 WORDTAG O posed
1 WORDTAG O 213,845
1 WORDTAG O 0*
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eusebio
1 WORDTAG O rationalised
3 WORDTAG O 12,700-12,800
98 WORDTAG O shares
1 WORDTAG O underwriting
1 WORDTAG O right-handed
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Torpedo
1 WORDTAG O 3.14
1 WORDTAG O MPS
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
2 WORDTAG O 10-2
2 WORDTAG O downwards
5 WORDTAG O 59th
1 WORDTAG O 1,156.79
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Red
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ravenna
1 WORDTAG O swallow
1 WORDTAG O gastro-intestinal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Economy
1 WORDTAG O 8.54
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zuleeg
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarians
1 WORDTAG O 690,000
1 WORDTAG O rampaging
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Trust
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Stagecoach
1 WORDTAG O mobilised
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Glentoran
3 WORDTAG O 3.3
1 WORDTAG I-PER Idriss
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Care
1 WORDTAG I-LOC AL-MUNTAR
21374 WORDTAG O _RARE_
1 WORDTAG O accessible
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pasok
1 WORDTAG O +34
5 WORDTAG O iron
1 WORDTAG O continent
3 WORDTAG O 1966
1 WORDTAG O resurgent
1 WORDTAG O 55-11-2324411
4 WORDTAG O flat
2 WORDTAG O reopening
1 WORDTAG O accusations
1 WORDTAG O kero
1 WORDTAG O compromising
2 WORDTAG O pre-abnormals
4 WORDTAG I-PER Brundle
1 WORDTAG O chain-smoking
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosia-Hercegovina
1 WORDTAG O 1652
1 WORDTAG O 9-0-41-1
1 WORDTAG O expectation
1 WORDTAG O 34-20
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem-led
1 WORDTAG O Superior
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Jaffray
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
1 WORDTAG O 111.50
13 WORDTAG O responsible
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Alsthom
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mavituna
1 WORDTAG O Named
1 WORDTAG O coerce
5 WORDTAG O set-top
1 WORDTAG O needy
8 WORDTAG O century
2 WORDTAG O technologies
1 WORDTAG O 81.12
1 WORDTAG O German-based
1 WORDTAG O referred
18 WORDTAG O range
1 WORDTAG O leaked
1 WORDTAG O appearing
2 WORDTAG O viscose
8 WORDTAG O SUMMARIES
2 WORDTAG I-PER Szymanski
1 WORDTAG O tractors
2 WORDTAG O planks
1 WORDTAG O 1,294.5
1 WORDTAG O 123-4
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dier
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ROTTERDAM
1 WORDTAG O HAT-TRICK
6 WORDTAG O highest
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Royal
2 WORDTAG O CRASH
8 WORDTAG O construction
1 WORDTAG O Clean
1 WORDTAG O ARANYAPRATHET
4 WORDTAG O dystrophin
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Seychelles
1 WORDTAG O rain-soaked
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Osaka
1 WORDTAG I-PER Manne
1 WORDTAG O insult
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Novorossiisk
2 WORDTAG O PROVS
4 WORDTAG I-ORG ORIOLES
3 WORDTAG I-LOC PRAGUE
1 WORDTAG O likes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bottomley
14 WORDTAG O seeking
1 WORDTAG O taunt
13 WORDTAG I-MISC RBI
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dadabhoy
1 WORDTAG O 408
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Beautiful
2 WORDTAG O legislators
362 WORDTAG O $
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NFU
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hafez
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bieszk
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lake
1 WORDTAG O soap
3 WORDTAG O two-out
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ham
1 WORDTAG O strengthening
1 WORDTAG I-PER SPOT
1 WORDTAG O hop
1 WORDTAG O fliers
1 WORDTAG O experiencing
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kostas
2 WORDTAG O Budget
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
1 WORDTAG O minimal
1 WORDTAG O penalise
2 WORDTAG O contention
2 WORDTAG O cancel
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherland
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tempelhof
7 WORDTAG O +301
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pecs
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
1 WORDTAG O 4:04.78
2 WORDTAG O resorts
3 WORDTAG O blacks
1 WORDTAG O publicity
1 WORDTAG O 102-0
1 WORDTAG O 6.03
1 WORDTAG O 26.00
1 WORDTAG O Eco
40 WORDTAG O scored
92 WORDTAG O while
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
1 WORDTAG O Described
8 WORDTAG O station
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bethlehem
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jonk
1 WORDTAG I-LOC 31
1 WORDTAG I-MISC DAVIS
1 WORDTAG O 39.7
2 WORDTAG O rib
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kamyshin
1 WORDTAG O battles
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Emeraud
1 WORDTAG O 1347
2 WORDTAG O 23.
1 WORDTAG O changeup
2 WORDTAG O FULL
1 WORDTAG O progressively
2 WORDTAG O shoes
1 WORDTAG O 21.75
1 WORDTAG I-ORG LANKADEEPA
4 WORDTAG O participation
1 WORDTAG O unfruitful
4 WORDTAG O 117
1 WORDTAG O rapists
1 WORDTAG I-LOC GROZNY
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Xamax
1 WORDTAG O 2030
1 WORDTAG O CHALLENGE
1 WORDTAG I-MISC POKKA
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ROVERETO
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kasparkova
1 WORDTAG O Pakistnn
3 WORDTAG O hijackings
5 WORDTAG O youth
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kapoor
4 WORDTAG O extraordinary
2 WORDTAG O compares
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AdOn
1 WORDTAG I-PER Claude
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Municipals
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jenrette
1 WORDTAG O forecaster
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hunte
1 WORDTAG O purchaser
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mirhunisa
1 WORDTAG O good-natured
4 WORDTAG O sixth-inning
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kekkila
36 WORDTAG O ban
2 WORDTAG I-PER Radka
2 WORDTAG O +0,2
4 WORDTAG O 51st
1 WORDTAG O 54.13
1 WORDTAG O scoured
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
1 WORDTAG O code
58 WORDTAG O deal
1 WORDTAG O 1,044
1 WORDTAG O upbeat
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Council
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vaughn
1 WORDTAG O short-dated
1 WORDTAG O flashlight
2 WORDTAG I-MISC CeBIT
1 WORDTAG O confederate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tuan
2 WORDTAG O sudden
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
1 WORDTAG O 340.00
1 WORDTAG O pima
17 WORDTAG O output
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
1 WORDTAG O breath
330 WORDTAG O would
20 WORDTAG O GB
1 WORDTAG O ostensibly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zhang
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
2 WORDTAG O 204.74
1 WORDTAG O robberies
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Arch
4 WORDTAG I-PER Moada
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leoni
1 WORDTAG O NAME
3 WORDTAG I-PER Boutros-Ghali
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fulke
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rafael
2 WORDTAG O 2183
3 WORDTAG O 210.00
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshopper
1 WORDTAG O ousting
2 WORDTAG I-PER DeJesus
1 WORDTAG O obligation
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Exploitation
1 WORDTAG O 5:17
1 WORDTAG I-LOC El
1 WORDTAG O 115,000
291 WORDTAG O out
1 WORDTAG O interpretations
9 WORDTAG O inflation
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Toyota
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Setubal
1 WORDTAG O 310.00
5 WORDTAG O merely
2 WORDTAG O 8.9
3 WORDTAG O sandwich
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Partnership
78 WORDTAG O should
1 WORDTAG O steamrollered
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Valletta
5 WORDTAG O grew
1 WORDTAG O lb-1
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Pokka
1 WORDTAG I-PER Basler
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boutoille
3 WORDTAG O predictions
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rene
1 WORDTAG O quashed
1 WORDTAG O prospector
1 WORDTAG O 10700
1 WORDTAG O HARD
1 WORDTAG O 566
1 WORDTAG O viable
1 WORDTAG O SOCIALISTS
16 WORDTAG I-LOC BRUSSELS
1 WORDTAG I-PER FERGUSON
3 WORDTAG O spirits
2 WORDTAG I-LOC GULF
1 WORDTAG O 7.85
2 WORDTAG O explicit
3 WORDTAG O brokered
1 WORDTAG O macroeconomic
9 WORDTAG O rating
11 WORDTAG I-PER Boardman
1 WORDTAG O 45.21
2 WORDTAG O high-profile
1 WORDTAG O defy
1 WORDTAG O conquered
1 WORDTAG O oversight
3 WORDTAG O locally
4 WORDTAG I-PER Ozers
2 WORDTAG O 42.5
3 WORDTAG O help-wanted
1 WORDTAG O 0.30
6 WORDTAG O Also
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gehrig
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Stabaek
1 WORDTAG O 97.34
4 WORDTAG I-PER Coulthard
3 WORDTAG O Farm
1 WORDTAG O non-core
1 WORDTAG O rubble
8 WORDTAG O abortion
1 WORDTAG O 9.050
66 WORDTAG O left
5 WORDTAG O blown
1 WORDTAG O glaciers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zarak
1 WORDTAG O tandem
1 WORDTAG O hometown
1 WORDTAG O EVOLUTION
1 WORDTAG O sunbed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC U.N.-sponsored
1 WORDTAG O Supercoppa
2 WORDTAG O high-yielding
2 WORDTAG O ringing
3 WORDTAG O .10
1 WORDTAG O arid
3 WORDTAG O .406
2 WORDTAG O post-match
1 WORDTAG O 391-seat
4 WORDTAG I-PER Conte
1 WORDTAG O hovercraft
3 WORDTAG O overwhelmingly
1 WORDTAG O urges
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vicenza
1 WORDTAG O 12:01
3 WORDTAG I-PER Okuda
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warburg
1 WORDTAG O greetings
1 WORDTAG O participated
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nastase
1 WORDTAG O RELATIONS
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
1 WORDTAG O sternly
1 WORDTAG O widely-reported
1 WORDTAG O part-finance
1 WORDTAG O passion
1 WORDTAG O 29/89
8 WORDTAG I-ORG MDS
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mugabe
5 WORDTAG O bush
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Tarmac
1 WORDTAG O 93.2
2 WORDTAG O install
1 WORDTAG O 123.89
8 WORDTAG O 160
1 WORDTAG O 2.60
1 WORDTAG I-PER Easley
1 WORDTAG O laboured
1 WORDTAG O 49.6
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tottenham
57 WORDTAG O cents
4 WORDTAG I-PER Rashid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barnes
2 WORDTAG I-PER Barros
1 WORDTAG O Deutsche
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bobic
1 WORDTAG O 662
1 WORDTAG O 95/96
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hack
2 WORDTAG O lagging
2 WORDTAG I-ORG MSK
1 WORDTAG O repatriate
1 WORDTAG O baked
2 WORDTAG O 8.29
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Ivory
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Zizkov
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rouxel
2 WORDTAG I-ORG WARWICKSHIRE
23 WORDTAG O 46
1 WORDTAG O 60.33
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interpol
1 WORDTAG O Commanders
3 WORDTAG O hundred
2 WORDTAG O seminar
3 WORDTAG O abusing
1 WORDTAG O behave
7 WORDTAG O stadium
2 WORDTAG O Leaders
1 WORDTAG O reasserting
4 WORDTAG O collective
1 WORDTAG O 279
1 WORDTAG O Wednesay
368 WORDTAG O been
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gorre
1 WORDTAG O 16th-century
2 WORDTAG O brighter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Todor
7 WORDTAG O cup
1 WORDTAG O slaying
1 WORDTAG O 13.1
5 WORDTAG O farms
2 WORDTAG O overhaul
1 WORDTAG O second-ranking
1 WORDTAG O sheets
1 WORDTAG O tuscan
2 WORDTAG I-LOC MIDEAST
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hradec
1 WORDTAG O 96/04
1 WORDTAG O preparations
1 WORDTAG O kidding
1 WORDTAG O 1:05.219
1 WORDTAG O 0.39
1 WORDTAG O defects
8 WORDTAG I-LOC COLORADO
2 WORDTAG I-LOC PHILADELPHIA
3 WORDTAG O bizarre
3 WORDTAG I-PER Goldman
1 WORDTAG O cameras
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Operation
1 WORDTAG O Beachcomber
1 WORDTAG O 2,341.5
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dahlan
2 WORDTAG O fiancee
1 WORDTAG O Grade
1 WORDTAG O lateral
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
1 WORDTAG O 1971
1 WORDTAG O Cholera
2 WORDTAG O missile
1 WORDTAG O 115.1
1 WORDTAG O cane
1 WORDTAG I-ORG FLNC
3 WORDTAG O combined
22 WORDTAG I-ORG NATO
37 WORDTAG O ministry
1 WORDTAG I-MISC LISPI
48 WORDTAG O OF
1 WORDTAG O waited
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Medellin
1 WORDTAG O Source
3 WORDTAG O Investigators
1 WORDTAG O 5,060
1 WORDTAG O gunshot
1 WORDTAG O volleyed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tanny
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tauranaga
2 WORDTAG O reorganisation
10 WORDTAG O carry
5 WORDTAG O searched
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Westerners
1 WORDTAG O 1.4789
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Editorial
2 WORDTAG I-ORG BNZ
1 WORDTAG O sun-baked
2 WORDTAG O filmed
58 WORDTAG O 72
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interior
1 WORDTAG I-PER Strunz
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
1 WORDTAG O 8.20-8.50
1 WORDTAG O +9.8
1 WORDTAG O 733.75
1 WORDTAG O publicists
2 WORDTAG O likened
1 WORDTAG O COMMANDOS
1 WORDTAG O RABN.CN
1 WORDTAG O Work
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Agdam
2 WORDTAG O 820
1 WORDTAG O irresponsible
3 WORDTAG O deter
1 WORDTAG O 1,421.90
2 WORDTAG O 11.12
8 WORDTAG I-PER Bourlet
1 WORDTAG O dizziness
1 WORDTAG I-MISC France
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Maccabi
1 WORDTAG O teething
1 WORDTAG O 1700
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
2 WORDTAG O MARKET
1 WORDTAG O sightseers
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
1 WORDTAG O Contrary
2 WORDTAG O frame
3 WORDTAG O long-time
1 WORDTAG O loophole
1 WORDTAG O collection
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blake
2 WORDTAG O +6221
5 WORDTAG O inquiry
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cor
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Tibetan
1 WORDTAG O 2-141
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bailard
1 WORDTAG O passionate
1 WORDTAG O co-producer
3 WORDTAG O testify
2 WORDTAG O Aircraft
1 WORDTAG O 165,150
1 WORDTAG O NovDec
1 WORDTAG O 705M
3 WORDTAG O 15-3
1 WORDTAG I-ORG SKS
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Mapourdit
1 WORDTAG O 353.24
1 WORDTAG I-PER Niclas
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jennifer
4 WORDTAG O Jan-April
4 WORDTAG O reference
3 WORDTAG I-PER Omar
2 WORDTAG O monopoly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Siraj
2 WORDTAG I-PER Noce
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
5 WORDTAG O procedure
1 WORDTAG I-PER Riel
1 WORDTAG O SUB
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazprom
1 WORDTAG O bearing
1 WORDTAG O BAN
1 WORDTAG O snatching
1 WORDTAG O DIVIDED
1 WORDTAG O 6.93
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Costa
1 WORDTAG O 6-26
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Alkhan-Yurt
1 WORDTAG O APRIL
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Curitiba
2 WORDTAG O Aa2
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Laboratories
2 WORDTAG O preference
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lees
1 WORDTAG O exposed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tijjani
1 WORDTAG O branding
1 WORDTAG O knocking
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Anatolian
1 WORDTAG O 995
1 WORDTAG O darker
2 WORDTAG O Here
1 WORDTAG O head-butting
1 WORDTAG O waterworks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rory
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
1 WORDTAG O 58-year-old
1 WORDTAG O 7950
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NTV
1 WORDTAG O 3,920.7
1 WORDTAG O nb-13
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Finns
1 WORDTAG O 10.19
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.960
1 WORDTAG O 26.93
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dakar
1 WORDTAG O divided
1 WORDTAG O BUS
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.006
2 WORDTAG O 576
3 WORDTAG O 730
1 WORDTAG O thoughts
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Lockhart
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
1 WORDTAG O mismanagement
1 WORDTAG O listing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Menendez
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Selection
4 WORDTAG O tankan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vnukovo
2 WORDTAG O misfortune
1 WORDTAG O 924
1 WORDTAG O disperse
45 WORDTAG O whether
1 WORDTAG O molest
2 WORDTAG O SERIES
7 WORDTAG O hot
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sexual
1 WORDTAG I-PER MULDER
29 WORDTAG O action
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marc-Vivien
40 WORDTAG O current
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Heart
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gente
1 WORDTAG O Acclaimed
9 WORDTAG O let
1 WORDTAG O feeding
1 WORDTAG O patrolling
1 WORDTAG O swoop
1 WORDTAG I-ORG FORMULA
4 WORDTAG O newly
1 WORDTAG I-LOC RICA
1 WORDTAG O nationally
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jari
1 WORDTAG O 48,800
1 WORDTAG O happier
3 WORDTAG O 1nb
1 WORDTAG O unnerved
53 WORDTAG O price
1 WORDTAG O mortars
2 WORDTAG O builders
2 WORDTAG O structured
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Baltasar
5 WORDTAG O spinal
2 WORDTAG O resulting
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wednesday
2 WORDTAG O 4.75
1 WORDTAG O 24.20
1 WORDTAG I-PER Malin
1 WORDTAG O squeeze
2 WORDTAG O vice-president
1 WORDTAG O nb-16
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fanton
1 WORDTAG I-PER Humayun
1 WORDTAG O Letter
10 WORDTAG O quite
2 WORDTAG O +6
1 WORDTAG I-ORG UHELNA
1 WORDTAG O bitterness
1 WORDTAG O uranium
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maase
1 WORDTAG O paparazzi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Frechette
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kschwendt
3 WORDTAG O substituted
1 WORDTAG O garnered
3 WORDTAG I-MISC TM
1 WORDTAG O 1:53.067
1 WORDTAG O limp
1 WORDTAG I-PER Camdzic
1 WORDTAG O half-century
1 WORDTAG O 36.0
28 WORDTAG O 76
1 WORDTAG O Absolute
1 WORDTAG I-PER McKenzie-Potter
1 WORDTAG O 15:04.94
1 WORDTAG O photocopies
2 WORDTAG O 5.1
1 WORDTAG O durum
4 WORDTAG O sixes
2 WORDTAG I-PER Baeron
1 WORDTAG O 31.0
1 WORDTAG O 3.27
2 WORDTAG O 2103
1 WORDTAG O dump
1 WORDTAG O newroom
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hamid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Claude
1 WORDTAG O stoke
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lihir
4 WORDTAG O 9-7
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Skhirat
1 WORDTAG O three-pointer
5 WORDTAG I-PER Brandes
12 WORDTAG O democracy
2 WORDTAG O consolidation
12 WORDTAG O sheep
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Confederation
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
1 WORDTAG O Apache
1 WORDTAG O clouds
1 WORDTAG O gaps
1 WORDTAG I-PER Batterby
1 WORDTAG O LOSE
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mallinckrodt
1 WORDTAG I-LOC TEGUCIGALPA
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Collingwood
1 WORDTAG O Long
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kinshasa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lisbet
1 WORDTAG O telephoned
2 WORDTAG O anxieties
2 WORDTAG O ought
7 WORDTAG O strikers
1 WORDTAG O SEEK
3 WORDTAG O 11.4
1 WORDTAG O 28.2
2 WORDTAG O translator
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gajadhar
1 WORDTAG O 2:39.00
1 WORDTAG O 91.05
2 WORDTAG O grouping
1 WORDTAG O 12,855.7
105 WORDTAG O statement
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pizzichini
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Havana
10 WORDTAG O New
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchnage
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
2 WORDTAG I-ORG BME
1 WORDTAG O 6.30
3 WORDTAG O SPOT
2 WORDTAG O infringement
1 WORDTAG O 30.9
1 WORDTAG O souls
1 WORDTAG O 15.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royce
4 WORDTAG I-LOC DELHI
1 WORDTAG I-ORG 1
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lila
1 WORDTAG O regards
2 WORDTAG I-PER Key
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Stung
4 WORDTAG I-PER Chapman
2 WORDTAG O sporting
5 WORDTAG O diesel
1 WORDTAG O performing
1 WORDTAG O 3-186
4 WORDTAG I-PER Crohn
6 WORDTAG O motion
1 WORDTAG O grey-haired
1 WORDTAG O mention
3 WORDTAG O infected
2 WORDTAG O hinterland
1 WORDTAG O shake-up
2 WORDTAG I-PER Narciso
1 WORDTAG O overseeing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sobotzik
2 WORDTAG I-ORG KSE
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pascolo
1 WORDTAG O 31.5
1 WORDTAG O apparel
2 WORDTAG O 8.05
1 WORDTAG O longer-term
1 WORDTAG O newcomers
1 WORDTAG O pro-rated
6 WORDTAG O leftist
3 WORDTAG O sensitive
6 WORDTAG O intent
1 WORDTAG I-PER Frederick
2 WORDTAG O 667
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Antioquia
1 WORDTAG O codename
1 WORDTAG O WALKOVER
1 WORDTAG I-MISC ,
3 WORDTAG O lamb
1 WORDTAG O suppose
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbertson
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Paralympics
51 WORDTAG O refugees
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rutherford
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
1 WORDTAG O 4000.00
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Zagreb
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pietro
1 WORDTAG O intrusions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Margret
1 WORDTAG O condos
1 WORDTAG O 6-0-29-1
2 WORDTAG I-PER Melanie
3 WORDTAG O humans
1 WORDTAG O one-out
22 WORDTAG O province
1 WORDTAG O 49-year-old
2 WORDTAG O praising
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Javedan
1 WORDTAG O breakout
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
1 WORDTAG I-ORG PSC
1 WORDTAG I-PER SHARPE
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nonferrous
1 WORDTAG I-PER Amina
1 WORDTAG O 941-434319
1 WORDTAG O uncontrolled
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Karachi
1 WORDTAG O JulAug
538 WORDTAG O his
2 WORDTAG O 97.82
2 WORDTAG I-ORG She'an
1 WORDTAG O pros
2 WORDTAG O desire
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Droits
1 WORDTAG O inlaid
7 WORDTAG O RALLYING
1 WORDTAG O fouled
1 WORDTAG O 100-2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Borg
2 WORDTAG O speeding
1 WORDTAG O Museum
92 WORDTAG O any
1 WORDTAG O 31.6
137 WORDTAG O We
1 WORDTAG O Premiership
6 WORDTAG O Operating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reuf
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Prima
4 WORDTAG O choose
31 WORDTAG O opening
1 WORDTAG O selecting
1 WORDTAG O 923
1 WORDTAG O 49.67
1 WORDTAG O pouring
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rasheed
1 WORDTAG O RUGBY
3 WORDTAG O accounted
2 WORDTAG I-PER Edwin
4 WORDTAG O indices
1 WORDTAG O 8-1
2 WORDTAG O tourism
1 WORDTAG I-PER Farrelly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vieira
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Chaser
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sloga
1 WORDTAG O soup
5 WORDTAG O therapy
2 WORDTAG O CURRENCIES
1 WORDTAG O 14.0
1 WORDTAG O finalising
1 WORDTAG O Domestic
16 WORDTAG O YR
12 WORDTAG O First
1 WORDTAG O 0.17
1 WORDTAG O pavilion
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Daughters
1 WORDTAG O co-operative
1 WORDTAG O bolts
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jacob
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
3 WORDTAG O 432
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Tromso
1 WORDTAG O invalidated
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Air
2 WORDTAG O widened
3 WORDTAG O reject
1 WORDTAG O outs
3 WORDTAG O 756525
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fletcher
1 WORDTAG O expel
1 WORDTAG O dumping
1 WORDTAG O 79.75
3 WORDTAG O H2
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ondruska
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barkho
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arthur
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ishwari
1 WORDTAG O chasing
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
1 WORDTAG O assailants
2 WORDTAG O 13.4
3 WORDTAG I-LOC RAMALLAH
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Liege
1 WORDTAG O .595
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Hong
1 WORDTAG O 1926
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hoechst
1 WORDTAG O BBB+
2 WORDTAG I-PER Belim
4 WORDTAG O launching
3 WORDTAG O 406
2 WORDTAG O enemies
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gogele
5 WORDTAG O sheet
2 WORDTAG O 6-8
1 WORDTAG O 0:06
1 WORDTAG O 2,342.0
93 WORDTAG I-LOC LONDON
1 WORDTAG O senator
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
1 WORDTAG O militarists
1 WORDTAG O spontaneous
1 WORDTAG O shoe
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostselmash
1 WORDTAG O ejected
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Brasov
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Nairobi
154 WORDTAG O more
1 WORDTAG O 1445
1 WORDTAG O shake
4 WORDTAG O +5
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Shabwa
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
1 WORDTAG O boosting
1 WORDTAG O 1,433.4
2 WORDTAG O 1998/99
2 WORDTAG O restrict
2 WORDTAG O outgoing
6 WORDTAG O hat-trick
8 WORDTAG O grade
1 WORDTAG O 13.66
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Watani
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Akron
2 WORDTAG O 1973
21 WORDTAG O profits
2 WORDTAG O procure
9 WORDTAG O population
1 WORDTAG O dearest
2 WORDTAG O 1950s
1 WORDTAG O splitting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Switzerland
2 WORDTAG O ill-fated
7 WORDTAG O margin
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Duluth
19 WORDTAG O member
3 WORDTAG O photograph
1 WORDTAG O 10-1-54-0
2 WORDTAG I-MISC 9002
1 WORDTAG O pop
12 WORDTAG O spending
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Aston
1 WORDTAG O 8p
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Vavuniya
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pignon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hasely
1 WORDTAG O Yeah
1 WORDTAG O panes
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
1 WORDTAG O fertile
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chabora
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sharma
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ravanelli
1 WORDTAG O Consulate
1 WORDTAG O calculated
1 WORDTAG O co-chairman
5 WORDTAG O destitute
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Atagi
2 WORDTAG O destined
1 WORDTAG O flood
1 WORDTAG B-MISC T-72
28 WORDTAG O analysts
2 WORDTAG O models
1 WORDTAG O 3,800
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ottoz
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toldo
1 WORDTAG O wigs
1 WORDTAG O 9-2-35-0
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Ashoknagar
1 WORDTAG O top-draw
1 WORDTAG O Consulate-General
2 WORDTAG O same-day
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Bohemians
1 WORDTAG O gloom-stricken
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shabana
136 WORDTAG O between
1 WORDTAG O credibility
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kid
1 WORDTAG O obstacles
1 WORDTAG I-PER Morariu
1 WORDTAG O 28:42.26
1 WORDTAG O 99
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hengelo
2 WORDTAG O hinted
24 WORDTAG O Net
3 WORDTAG O Revised
1 WORDTAG O 7-1-29-1
1 WORDTAG O shave
44 WORDTAG O higher
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gaissmayer
2 WORDTAG I-MISC CJD
4 WORDTAG O seeds
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bolger
3 WORDTAG I-PER VanLandingham
1 WORDTAG O disposals
1 WORDTAG O matured
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hinckley
1 WORDTAG O 18-14
1 WORDTAG O 10,056.4
1 WORDTAG O test-tube
4 WORDTAG O monetary
1 WORDTAG O 32,900-33,000
2 WORDTAG O manual
2 WORDTAG I-PER Horvath
1 WORDTAG O 251/01
32 WORDTAG O possible
2 WORDTAG O academics
1 WORDTAG O ignored
34 WORDTAG O 59
4 WORDTAG O pesos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lavaggi
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Biblical
1 WORDTAG I-LOC HIGHLANDS
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
1 WORDTAG O Towards
2 WORDTAG O +22
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Adelaide
1 WORDTAG O 51.80
4 WORDTAG I-PER Reneberg
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cimicchi
3 WORDTAG O Hijacked
8 WORDTAG O comments
3 WORDTAG O proprietary
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Agent
1 WORDTAG O whisk
1 WORDTAG O 506
6 WORDTAG O .504
1 WORDTAG O moult
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shamay
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pamire
1 WORDTAG O interpreted
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nieves
1 WORDTAG O bureaucrats
1 WORDTAG O 273-5
2 WORDTAG O wreckage
1 WORDTAG O 93.12
1 WORDTAG I-ORG One
1 WORDTAG O weaken
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Duessseldorf
1 WORDTAG O prone
4 WORDTAG O scorer
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dahl
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Universe
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
1 WORDTAG O fast-moving
1 WORDTAG I-PER Trueman
1 WORDTAG O 26-29
2 WORDTAG O lists
1 WORDTAG O 133.82
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnian-Croat
1 WORDTAG O w-9
1 WORDTAG O wallets
2 WORDTAG O erratically
106 WORDTAG O did
53 WORDTAG O get
4 WORDTAG I-ORG MOODY
1 WORDTAG O middle-distance
3 WORDTAG O pensions
1 WORDTAG O 18,278
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Shanghai-Ek
2 WORDTAG I-PER POLLOCK
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Opera
2 WORDTAG O refuel
1 WORDTAG O 5.602
1 WORDTAG O 7000
1 WORDTAG O tendencies
1 WORDTAG O U.N
7 WORDTAG O N
1 WORDTAG I-PER Folha
3 WORDTAG O nb-8
1 WORDTAG O 6-1-23-2
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Bystrica
1 WORDTAG O 14-6
2 WORDTAG O fully
1 WORDTAG O last-place
1 WORDTAG O 7546
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Fairmont
1 WORDTAG O lashed
2 WORDTAG O Op
2 WORDTAG O prerequisite
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Disney
1 WORDTAG I-PER Madhusudan
1 WORDTAG O cinnamon
1 WORDTAG O electorate
4 WORDTAG O PRO-BASEBALL
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Longyearbyen
1 WORDTAG O 1.5497
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lumir
2 WORDTAG I-PER Roche
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lyman
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Yosu
18 WORDTAG O jail
2 WORDTAG O Corporate
1 WORDTAG O shrank
1 WORDTAG O energies
1 WORDTAG I-PER Firmin
167 WORDTAG O 1996-08-28
1 WORDTAG O leasing
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kamio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Howe
2 WORDTAG O 13-year
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hekmatyar
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Estudiantes
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wroclaw
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
1 WORDTAG O entertain
1 WORDTAG O Official
1 WORDTAG I-PER Makarov
1 WORDTAG O 1415
6 WORDTAG O blame
2 WORDTAG O Q3
1 WORDTAG O 6-mth
1 WORDTAG O cantons
1 WORDTAG O 1,119.0
1 WORDTAG O 54,800
2 WORDTAG O principle
5 WORDTAG O contacts
1 WORDTAG O 020-504-5040
1 WORDTAG O ring
1 WORDTAG O 7-1-24-0
1 WORDTAG O 2.78
2 WORDTAG O invaded
1 WORDTAG I-LOC KABUL
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sicily
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agyepong
1 WORDTAG O AGENCY
6 WORDTAG I-MISC RUGBY
2 WORDTAG O occur
97 WORDTAG O n't
1 WORDTAG O 3:33.00
3 WORDTAG I-PER Moya
2 WORDTAG O advising
25 WORDTAG O attacks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Martyn
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AL-WATAN
1 WORDTAG O Bomb
199 WORDTAG O told
1 WORDTAG O +0.7
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bratislava
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Career
1 WORDTAG O LATE
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Commonwealth
1 WORDTAG O anchored
4 WORDTAG I-PER Toure
4 WORDTAG O CBOT
4 WORDTAG O 1,600
121 WORDTAG O Minister
1 WORDTAG O NINTH
2 WORDTAG O Information
1 WORDTAG O 49.31
2 WORDTAG O 0.63
1 WORDTAG O windfall
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Dream
1 WORDTAG O mount
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Fontaine
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mayor
1 WORDTAG O 15.09
1 WORDTAG I-PER Edmonds
1 WORDTAG O 9-1-49-0
11 WORDTAG O born
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nano
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hoogma
4 WORDTAG O migration
1 WORDTAG O winningest
2 WORDTAG O capitalisation
3 WORDTAG I-ORG LKS
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
1 WORDTAG O discarding
1 WORDTAG O stabbings
2 WORDTAG O orderly
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
3 WORDTAG O separate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brenden
1 WORDTAG O Continent
1 WORDTAG O 19,734.70
1 WORDTAG I-PER Stephenson
2 WORDTAG I-PER Davids
1 WORDTAG O sectoral
1 WORDTAG O assignment
1 WORDTAG O aegis
1 WORDTAG O 8.45
1 WORDTAG O exculpated
1 WORDTAG O 2.50-3.0
2 WORDTAG O whistle-stop
1 WORDTAG O parred
1 WORDTAG O subsequent
1 WORDTAG I-PER Durham
1 WORDTAG O degrading
1 WORDTAG O lasts
5 WORDTAG O isolated
2 WORDTAG O 76.6
3 WORDTAG O Spaniards
2 WORDTAG O excessive
5 WORDTAG O autumn
1 WORDTAG O witchdoctor
4 WORDTAG O canteen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Timothy
1 WORDTAG O 3.334
3 WORDTAG O mid-August
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Venray
1 WORDTAG O COACHING
2 WORDTAG O ploughed
4 WORDTAG O insurer
1 WORDTAG O oilfields
1 WORDTAG I-PER Andres
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Guide
2 WORDTAG O superbike
5 WORDTAG O detective
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ferdy
1 WORDTAG O poetic
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Adelt
57 WORDTAG O race
3 WORDTAG O FOURTH
1 WORDTAG I-PER FOWLER
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jordi
1 WORDTAG O Producers
1 WORDTAG O HAND
1 WORDTAG O baggage
1 WORDTAG O COMMAND
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Churches
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Red
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Poznan
6 WORDTAG O m
1 WORDTAG O motorists
1 WORDTAG O distracting
1 WORDTAG O dismantle
1 WORDTAG O co-owned
1 WORDTAG O rectify
1 WORDTAG O barbarity
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ebe
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rohren
2 WORDTAG I-PER Richter
1 WORDTAG O preventative
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Palermo
1 WORDTAG O 11.60
1 WORDTAG O 196.8
30 WORDTAG O 48
1 WORDTAG O Undersecretary-General
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb-held
1 WORDTAG O 15-hour
1 WORDTAG O 218.50
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Udinese
2 WORDTAG O Highs
1 WORDTAG O 5-0
10 WORDTAG O crude
1 WORDTAG O reinsurance
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
1 WORDTAG O 1:05.406
1 WORDTAG O Social-Democratic
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
1 WORDTAG O 1781
1 WORDTAG O 4.62
1 WORDTAG O ostracism
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
1 WORDTAG I-LOC LJUBLJANA
2 WORDTAG O routing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Double
1 WORDTAG O stimulant
1 WORDTAG O item
6 WORDTAG O 170
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Welspun
525 WORDTAG O be
2 WORDTAG I-PER Silvio
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wilander
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jerzy
1 WORDTAG O 12,750-12,950
1 WORDTAG O umpire
1 WORDTAG O Lt.
1 WORDTAG O anxious
1 WORDTAG O 26:43.53
1 WORDTAG O 20-minute
2 WORDTAG O Maturity
1 WORDTAG O 5-1/3
1 WORDTAG O inexorable
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sourav
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Shaba
1 WORDTAG O 16,909,000
1 WORDTAG O 788
1 WORDTAG O .434
1 WORDTAG I-PER Galarraga
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Caufield
1 WORDTAG O artist
1 WORDTAG O Shutdown
1 WORDTAG O DOPING
5 WORDTAG O artillery
1 WORDTAG O 61st
1 WORDTAG O historically
3 WORDTAG I-PER Casey
4 WORDTAG I-PER Terence
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hollandsworth
1 WORDTAG O 8.20
1 WORDTAG O willingness
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Iran
5 WORDTAG O nurses
11 WORDTAG I-MISC 1,000
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
1 WORDTAG O dipping
1 WORDTAG O Twenty-five
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dynamics
1 WORDTAG O gaining
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vileujeux
50 WORDTAG O economic
1 WORDTAG O rigorous
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Flour
1 WORDTAG I-PER Donwahi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pearson
25 WORDTAG O After
2 WORDTAG O 43.0
2 WORDTAG O corporations
1 WORDTAG O iscovered
1 WORDTAG O knock-on
1 WORDTAG O locks
3 WORDTAG O run-scoring
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Jewish
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shimaponda
2 WORDTAG I-PER Whitlinger
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arias
1 WORDTAG O overreacted
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Huracan-Corrientes
1 WORDTAG O derivatives
1 WORDTAG O disgrace
1 WORDTAG I-ORG PO
3 WORDTAG I-ORG FFK
4 WORDTAG O ankle
2 WORDTAG O drilled
2 WORDTAG O mill
4 WORDTAG O spots
6 WORDTAG O dragged
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
1 WORDTAG I-ORG GIANTS
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NS
1 WORDTAG O 0.98
335 WORDTAG O beat
3 WORDTAG O BONDS
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Implats
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Bessemer
1 WORDTAG O shipload
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sawy
1 WORDTAG O 1:55.281
3 WORDTAG I-ORG SIMEX
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fiona
1 WORDTAG O cost-effective
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Boca
2 WORDTAG O 2-1-4-0
1 WORDTAG O 3.72
1 WORDTAG O technicalities
4 WORDTAG I-PER al-Kabariti
44 WORDTAG O 65
2 WORDTAG O congressmen
24 WORDTAG O big
1 WORDTAG I-PER Underwood
1 WORDTAG O 27:18.84
1 WORDTAG O STEEL
8 WORDTAG O happened
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sud-PTT
1 WORDTAG O jittery
1 WORDTAG O 49.06
12 WORDTAG O contact
1 WORDTAG O sheltering
2 WORDTAG I-PER Steeb
117 WORDTAG O four
1 WORDTAG O selector
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
2 WORDTAG O grammes
1 WORDTAG O 2-24
1 WORDTAG O pinch-hits
2 WORDTAG O temperature
1 WORDTAG I-PER Christina
1 WORDTAG O letdowns
1 WORDTAG O 12-1
1 WORDTAG O Bare
2 WORDTAG O 20.19
1 WORDTAG O hides
1 WORDTAG O solved
4 WORDTAG I-LOC LUMPUR
1 WORDTAG O 7,391
1 WORDTAG O 3.01
1 WORDTAG I-ORG a.s.
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
1 WORDTAG O judgement
2 WORDTAG O adoptive
26 WORDTAG O One
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gene
1 WORDTAG O Fifth-seed
2 WORDTAG O Higher
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pas
7 WORDTAG O bullish
1 WORDTAG O issuance
1 WORDTAG O DANCE
1 WORDTAG O 3/1/90
3 WORDTAG I-PER Axworthy
3 WORDTAG O indeed
1 WORDTAG O build-to-order
1 WORDTAG O 1754
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
1 WORDTAG O objection
2 WORDTAG O lords
1 WORDTAG O rob
1 WORDTAG I-PER Booy
30 WORDTAG I-ORG YORK
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agota
1 WORDTAG O 96.00
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Export
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Koninklijke
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tan
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pueblo
1 WORDTAG I-PER Medeghini
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Tobago
1 WORDTAG I-PER Biljana
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jadeja
4 WORDTAG O tower
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bari
1 WORDTAG I-ORG DLJ
1 WORDTAG O 2-15
1 WORDTAG O map
1 WORDTAG O floating-rate
1 WORDTAG O Determined
4 WORDTAG O birth
1 WORDTAG O retaliation
1 WORDTAG O 17.5
2 WORDTAG O 4-90
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sabourin
1 WORDTAG I-LOC CHILPANCINGO
2 WORDTAG O 11.3
1 WORDTAG O 33.2
1 WORDTAG O over-charging
1 WORDTAG O whirlwind
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Riel
2 WORDTAG O warring
1 WORDTAG O coat-tails
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Techs
1 WORDTAG O 55.66
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Siofok
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dreekman
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nutricia
1 WORDTAG O lax
1 WORDTAG I-PER Geronimo
2 WORDTAG I-MISC SUPERCUP
1 WORDTAG O 52.90
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Purefoods
1 WORDTAG I-ORG NBC
1 WORDTAG I-MISC MRI
1 WORDTAG O notation
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nitto
30 WORDTAG I-ORG NEW
1 WORDTAG O +15,272
1 WORDTAG O wraps
4 WORDTAG O Defenders
1 WORDTAG O Meng
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Ferrari
3 WORDTAG O brain
1 WORDTAG O Pace
2 WORDTAG O 0.8
1 WORDTAG O eighteen
1 WORDTAG O 413
9 WORDTAG O registered
1 WORDTAG O notorious
1 WORDTAG O 1,453
1 WORDTAG O Welcome
1 WORDTAG O 20.0
1 WORDTAG O minerals
32 WORDTAG O further
9 WORDTAG O registrations
24 WORDTAG O great
1 WORDTAG O world-class
1 WORDTAG O accomplish
1 WORDTAG O 2:42
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gibs
1 WORDTAG O 11.833
1 WORDTAG O 7:32.44
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mont-sur-Marchienne
1 WORDTAG O 2-16
1 WORDTAG O binding
1 WORDTAG O amyotrophic
132 WORDTAG O other
1 WORDTAG I-PER RAVANELLI
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Argyle
1 WORDTAG O carburettor
1 WORDTAG O 3-0-24-1
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Fame
1 WORDTAG O Rain
2 WORDTAG O provisional
1 WORDTAG O 1,452-km
1 WORDTAG O 300,962
1 WORDTAG O maternity
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
3 WORDTAG O relationship
2 WORDTAG O 560
1 WORDTAG O +9
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hambrecht
1 WORDTAG O January-April
21 WORDTAG O really
1 WORDTAG O ltd
1 WORDTAG O 100=1990
1 WORDTAG O DEFEAT
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Aldi
1 WORDTAG O Sellers
1 WORDTAG O 10-30
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nunung
6 WORDTAG I-MISC S.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Marrakesh
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Roussel
2 WORDTAG O Sheep
1 WORDTAG O stream
4 WORDTAG O relatives
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
1 WORDTAG I-PER Werdel
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmad
1 WORDTAG O Junior
1 WORDTAG O Clashes
1 WORDTAG O comparable
1 WORDTAG O 2,389
3 WORDTAG O formation
1 WORDTAG O Mortgage
1 WORDTAG I-PER CROFT
1 WORDTAG O 74-year
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lofton
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bossi
1 WORDTAG O vomitoxin
4 WORDTAG O bases-loaded
1 WORDTAG I-MISC China-bound
1 WORDTAG O 25.0-27.0
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Palmans
22 WORDTAG O defeat
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
1 WORDTAG O dividenD
1 WORDTAG I-PER MARTINEZ
1 WORDTAG O whitewater
22 WORDTAG O ninth
1 WORDTAG O 1,123
2 WORDTAG O non-traditional
2 WORDTAG O REASONS
1 WORDTAG O conclude
1 WORDTAG B-LOC Israel
105 WORDTAG O win
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Caja
1 WORDTAG O 3-8/16
1 WORDTAG O domestically
1 WORDTAG O emerges
1 WORDTAG I-PER Munk
5 WORDTAG O showers
4 WORDTAG I-LOC KUALA
4 WORDTAG O Dr.
1 WORDTAG O safer
1 WORDTAG I-ORG self-rule
1 WORDTAG O forfeit
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jui
1 WORDTAG I-PER Polverino
2 WORDTAG O chiefs
1 WORDTAG O re-examined
1 WORDTAG I-PER Renteria
214 WORDTAG O also
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cercle
1 WORDTAG O hideaway
1 WORDTAG O intervened
2 WORDTAG O tentative
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Drug
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kranich
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
1 WORDTAG O 1.4871
2 WORDTAG O Expectations
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wieczorek
74 WORDTAG O end
6 WORDTAG O sharply
1 WORDTAG O assemble
3 WORDTAG O flowing
689 WORDTAG O is
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
2 WORDTAG O bitter
1 WORDTAG O 3.05
1 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNETONKA
1 WORDTAG O 11.34
3 WORDTAG O persons
2 WORDTAG O majorities
4 WORDTAG I-PER Demel
1 WORDTAG O payout
46 WORDTAG O 1-0
1 WORDTAG O dig
1 WORDTAG O Delegates
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aoki
1 WORDTAG O organizers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Deletraz
11 WORDTAG O servants
1 WORDTAG I-PER Adolf
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
1 WORDTAG O 728-9560
1 WORDTAG O wood
1 WORDTAG I-LOC AL
1 WORDTAG O juvenile
1 WORDTAG O 4/94
1 WORDTAG I-PER Schweitzer
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Himalayan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Llaneras
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Uppsala
1 WORDTAG I-LOC CALGARY
6 WORDTAG O self-rule
1 WORDTAG O sacrificed
1 WORDTAG O 16.63
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Minerals
3 WORDTAG I-PER Domingos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ivar
1 WORDTAG O +65
1 WORDTAG O 07.00
1 WORDTAG O unemployement
1 WORDTAG O 3,292
1 WORDTAG O survival
1 WORDTAG O SUPER
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Allahyar
1 WORDTAG O 47.99
2 WORDTAG O forever
3 WORDTAG O exploration
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Boltfelag
1 WORDTAG I-PER Grzybowska
1 WORDTAG O 951
1 WORDTAG O inundating
1 WORDTAG O insurgency-related
1 WORDTAG O 72-0
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Montserrat
12 WORDTAG O computer
2 WORDTAG O 900.00
2 WORDTAG O arranged
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Leveilly
19 WORDTAG O 57
1 WORDTAG O placate
1 WORDTAG I-ORG DNEVNI
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.588
2 WORDTAG I-PER Crafar
3 WORDTAG O outfielder
1 WORDTAG O percentile
1 WORDTAG O abiding
1 WORDTAG O analyzing
1 WORDTAG O managements
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vriesde
2 WORDTAG O HOCKEY
3 WORDTAG O SALES
1 WORDTAG O Change
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gobert
5 WORDTAG O 10.5
25 WORDTAG O letter
3 WORDTAG O norms
4 WORDTAG I-PER B.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vidal-Quadras
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Eslami
1 WORDTAG O Testing
1 WORDTAG O vowing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ihlas
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Heidrun
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ALKHAN-YURT
3 WORDTAG O 11-4
1 WORDTAG O 75.912
1 WORDTAG O punishable
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Doetinchem
1 WORDTAG O 7,138
3 WORDTAG O cholera
3 WORDTAG O 109.4
2 WORDTAG O 2,383
3 WORDTAG O flooded
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kabul
4 WORDTAG I-ORG In
1 WORDTAG O 51.00
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Riyadh
1 WORDTAG O 61.2
1 WORDTAG O f...
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nagatsuka
2 WORDTAG O alloy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Caroline
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshoppers
1 WORDTAG O long-barreled
2 WORDTAG O escorted
1 WORDTAG O jury
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Housing
1 WORDTAG O 5.83
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottinghamshire
1 WORDTAG I-LOC IA
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
2 WORDTAG O above-average
1 WORDTAG O four-set
3 WORDTAG O Quarterly
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BUENOS
5 WORDTAG O fix
1 WORDTAG O 2:01.98
4 WORDTAG I-PER Frentzen
2 WORDTAG I-MISC AEX
4 WORDTAG O resuming
1 WORDTAG O writings
1 WORDTAG O recognizing
1 WORDTAG O hijacker
2 WORDTAG O incomprehensible
1 WORDTAG O Capt
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sithole
1 WORDTAG O 42.00
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Genk
4 WORDTAG O camera
2 WORDTAG I-PER Prodi
1 WORDTAG O free-kick
4 WORDTAG O bound
1 WORDTAG O 1-for-2
19 WORDTAG O saw
1 WORDTAG O newly-promoted
2 WORDTAG O 374
1 WORDTAG I-MISC MILLS
1 WORDTAG O overstayer
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ruuttu
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jian
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Guelfs
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cejka
1 WORDTAG O scapegoat
2 WORDTAG I-PER Valentin
1 WORDTAG O novitiate
1 WORDTAG O life-sustaining
2 WORDTAG O principal
5 WORDTAG O imported
1 WORDTAG I-PER Babayan
1 WORDTAG O 0:08
1 WORDTAG I-PER Farina
3 WORDTAG O fierce
1 WORDTAG O 3-0-15-0
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Fighter
1 WORDTAG O scalp
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bench
40 WORDTAG O STANDINGS
1 WORDTAG O pack
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aitken
2 WORDTAG I-PER Begum
2 WORDTAG O 3.98
2 WORDTAG O serial
2 WORDTAG O grandparents
1 WORDTAG O 206,464
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Macedonian
1 WORDTAG O stunts
1 WORDTAG O 1716
3 WORDTAG I-PER Srinath
1 WORDTAG I-PER Symcox
2 WORDTAG O PRACTICE
8 WORDTAG O try
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anthony
1 WORDTAG O desolate
1 WORDTAG O 610,000
5 WORDTAG O trend
2 WORDTAG O lawmakers
1 WORDTAG O joke
1 WORDTAG O industrialists
1 WORDTAG O 53112
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Merchant
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cruzeiro
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jose-Maria
3 WORDTAG O creating
1 WORDTAG O Sep.96
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tchmil
1 WORDTAG O 1.215
2 WORDTAG O loud
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mohali
13 WORDTAG O defeated
2 WORDTAG I-MISC NATO-led
1 WORDTAG O contracting
2 WORDTAG O Trading
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nicky
1 WORDTAG O Promo
1 WORDTAG I-PER Campora
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gowda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yuan-dong
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jacky
1 WORDTAG O penal
1 WORDTAG O 72nd
2 WORDTAG I-PER BOARDMAN
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bada
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kingdom
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kuperman
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.884
1 WORDTAG O J
1 WORDTAG O 1944
1 WORDTAG O Investment
1 WORDTAG O labor
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sfeir
5 WORDTAG O painted
1 WORDTAG O 18.40
2 WORDTAG O 10no
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stafford
5 WORDTAG O Add
1 WORDTAG O Hovercrafts
1 WORDTAG O LIFTS
8 WORDTAG O gunman
33 WORDTAG O press
4 WORDTAG O spreading
1 WORDTAG O flour
2 WORDTAG O 425
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Homeland
33 WORDTAG O yet
2 WORDTAG I-PER Harden
1 WORDTAG O famished
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Trepca
3 WORDTAG O boys
2 WORDTAG O after-hours
3 WORDTAG O pageant
2 WORDTAG O bullet
1 WORDTAG O thumbs
1 WORDTAG O Something
767 WORDTAG O that
1 WORDTAG O 48.86
1 WORDTAG O soars
1 WORDTAG O 1:52.354
1 WORDTAG I-PER Virgilius
1 WORDTAG O 25.0
2 WORDTAG I-PER Boraine
2 WORDTAG I-PER Pescosolido
2 WORDTAG O Team
1 WORDTAG O Message
1 WORDTAG O forked
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Alicante
2 WORDTAG O 9,800
1 WORDTAG O truly
1 WORDTAG I-ORG VOIE
1 WORDTAG O 7.77
1 WORDTAG O intentionally
1 WORDTAG I-LOC CHESAPEAKE
1 WORDTAG O 3.50-4.00
1 WORDTAG O cattle-on-feed
23 WORDTAG O Played
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 2913/92
1 WORDTAG O 50,400
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Interbank
2 WORDTAG O negotiate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lakpe
5 WORDTAG O Chief
4 WORDTAG O doubts
1 WORDTAG O post-handover
1 WORDTAG O fortnight
1 WORDTAG I-ORG TABAK
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Woodlands
1 WORDTAG O 0815
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shaughnessy
1 WORDTAG O friction
1 WORDTAG O occasional
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cheuvreux
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dubnica
8 WORDTAG I-PER Perry
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Carrefour
1 WORDTAG O 624
2 WORDTAG O pays
1 WORDTAG O out-of-town
2 WORDTAG O interrupted
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vasilopoulos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Redmond
1 WORDTAG O 973
1 WORDTAG I-ORG ANP
1 WORDTAG O 62.50
1 WORDTAG O parking
6 WORDTAG O weapon
2 WORDTAG O 0.47
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jamir
1 WORDTAG O Miners
1 WORDTAG O Commem
4 WORDTAG O helping
1 WORDTAG O seals
1 WORDTAG O COAL
1 WORDTAG O 312-408-8647
1 WORDTAG O fully-elected
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bobbie
3 WORDTAG O bowed
4 WORDTAG O storage
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Marxist-Leninist
8 WORDTAG O begins
1 WORDTAG O .431
1 WORDTAG O conquering
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Donaldson
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Umbria
1 WORDTAG O 123rd-ranked
4 WORDTAG I-PER Boutros
1 WORDTAG I-PER Susana
1 WORDTAG O portends
1 WORDTAG O 1.07
1 WORDTAG O longtime
2 WORDTAG O triumphal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AHRONOTH
9 WORDTAG O two-run
1 WORDTAG O Messages
3 WORDTAG O arrive
2 WORDTAG O nabs
1 WORDTAG O consolidate
2 WORDTAG O uneven
1 WORDTAG O ineffective
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cadete
1 WORDTAG O overreacting
1 WORDTAG O Containment
1 WORDTAG O 5,539
2 WORDTAG O elite
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.778
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fenerbahce
1 WORDTAG I-ORG CLINTON
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ravindra
1 WORDTAG O 988.2
1 WORDTAG O ++359-2
15 WORDTAG O list
5 WORDTAG O 398
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Venalum
1 WORDTAG O fifth-ranked
1 WORDTAG O 25-YEAR
1 WORDTAG O prematurely
1 WORDTAG O 0645
1 WORDTAG O 1995-96
1 WORDTAG O 193
5 WORDTAG O consulate
5 WORDTAG I-MISC ADRs
22 WORDTAG O player
2 WORDTAG I-PER Miladin
1 WORDTAG O afflicted
71 WORDTAG O 22
1 WORDTAG O compromised
1 WORDTAG O +361
1 WORDTAG O .444
2 WORDTAG I-ORG CAF
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cukurova
1 WORDTAG I-MISC LDP-dominated
1 WORDTAG O questionable
1 WORDTAG O 59440
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Zealands
6 WORDTAG O resulted
1 WORDTAG O romantically
7 WORDTAG I-PER Reeve
1 WORDTAG I-PER MALEEVA
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Hampshire
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian-made
1 WORDTAG O harmless
1 WORDTAG O references
1 WORDTAG O 4-102
27 WORDTAG O title
1 WORDTAG O private-sector
2 WORDTAG O administered
2 WORDTAG O rings
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Opel
3 WORDTAG O congressional
1 WORDTAG O PREDICTION
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Leon
3 WORDTAG I-PER Clavet
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Maniema
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BARUM
1 WORDTAG O 15-share
1 WORDTAG O remedy
1 WORDTAG O editions
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Boeing
2 WORDTAG O firearm
1 WORDTAG O prft
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pope
1 WORDTAG O 6-0-47-0
5 WORDTAG O lions
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Subsidiaries
1 WORDTAG O Vivit
1 WORDTAG O comic
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Jiul
52 WORDTAG O agency
3 WORDTAG O reward
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Silicon
1 WORDTAG I-LOC NORWAY
1 WORDTAG O 2.10
1 WORDTAG I-PER Santapaola
2 WORDTAG I-PER Likhovtseva
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sorrento
1 WORDTAG O AA3
5 WORDTAG O push
1 WORDTAG O goaless
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lefevre
1 WORDTAG O .552
1 WORDTAG I-PER Luminzu
2 WORDTAG I-ORG HCFA
2 WORDTAG O pumps
1 WORDTAG I-PER Miron
1 WORDTAG I-MISC and
1 WORDTAG O 450
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Tutsi-dominated
1 WORDTAG O 128-member
2 WORDTAG O SIGNS
1 WORDTAG O EASE
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Place
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gras
1 WORDTAG O dared
1 WORDTAG O TEA
13 WORDTAG O mad
2 WORDTAG O sq
1 WORDTAG O flushed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vaccari
1 WORDTAG O 201
2 WORDTAG O testosterone
1 WORDTAG O 867.100
1 WORDTAG O redraw
1 WORDTAG I-PER SALAH
26 WORDTAG O reached
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Biehl
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Zeneca
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ewe
5 WORDTAG O heading
1 WORDTAG O reservations
15 WORDTAG I-PER Mike
1 WORDTAG O north-west
1 WORDTAG O 19.4
2 WORDTAG O prisons
1 WORDTAG I-PER CHANG
5 WORDTAG O recorded
1 WORDTAG O emergent
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Creedmoor
1 WORDTAG O spirited
2 WORDTAG I-PER Snyman
3 WORDTAG O non-trade
1 WORDTAG O laughed
1 WORDTAG O second-placed
1 WORDTAG O 58.00
2 WORDTAG O endorsement
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Times
1 WORDTAG O regalia
4 WORDTAG O computers
3 WORDTAG O tells
1 WORDTAG O intra-day
2 WORDTAG O 208.442
1 WORDTAG O Dec.
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Museum
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Super
2 WORDTAG I-PER Citterio
1 WORDTAG I-PER O'Donnell
5 WORDTAG O .457
1 WORDTAG O uncompromising
